Generate a UML use case diagram code for the description based on the following requirements in a proper syntatically way : {'entities': [('March 20, 2002', 'DATE'), ('1', 'CARDINAL'), ('Standard Co-Emulation Modeling \nInterface', 'ORG'), ('SCE-MI', 'ORG'), ('John Stickley', 'PERSON'), ('Duaine Pryor', 'PERSON'), ('SCE', 'ORG'), ('2001', 'DATE'), ('Ikos Systems, Inc.', 'ORG'), ('NDA', 'ORG'), ('SCE', 'ORG'), ('C/C++', 'ORG'), ('DUT', 'ORG'), ('DUT', 'ORG'), ('Ikos Systems', 'ORG'), ('79', 'CARDINAL'), ('Great Oaks Blvd', 'FAC'), ('San Jose', 'GPE'), ('CA 95119SCE-API\nStandard Co-Emulation API \nConsortium\nRevision', 'PRODUCT'), ('1.0Introduction', 'CARDINAL'), ('2', 'CARDINAL'), ('94', 'CARDINAL'), ('SCE', 'ORG'), ('1.1', 'CARDINAL'), ('EDA', 'ORG'), ('SoC', 'ORG'), ('10 years ago', 'DATE'), ('the next 10 years', 'DATE'), ('SCE', 'ORG'), ('today', 'DATE'), ('today', 'DATE'), ('API', 'ORG'), ('1.1.2', 'CARDINAL'), ('VHDL PLI', 'PERSON'), ('1.2', 'CARDINAL'), ('the Standard Co-Emulation API  (', 'ORG'), ('SCE-API', 'ORG'), ('EDA', 'ORG'), ('EDA', 'ORG'), ('API', 'ORG'), ('Aptix', 'ORG'), ('Ikos Systems', 'ORG'), ('Mentor Graphics', 'ORG'), ('ST Microelectronics,', 'ORG'), ('Synopsys', 'PERSON'), ('TransEDA', 'ORG'), ('SCE-MI', 'ORG'), ('SCE', 'ORG'), ('SCE-API', 'ORG'), ('SCE', 'ORG'), ('SCE', 'ORG'), ('SoC', 'ORG'), ('SCE-MI', 'ORG'), ('3', 'CARDINAL'), ('1.4', 'CARDINAL'), ('Acronyms', 'PERSON'), ('BCA', 'ORG'), ('RTL', 'ORG'), ('Date Revised', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('1.0', 'CARDINAL'), ('12-11-00', 'TIME'), ('Pryor Initial', 'PERSON'), ('SCE', 'ORG'), ('Oct. 2000', 'DATE'), ('Paris', 'GPE'), ('France', 'GPE'), ('1.2', 'CARDINAL'), ('John Stickley Revised', 'PERSON'), ('second', 'ORDINAL'), ('SCE', 'ORG'), ('Dec 14-15', 'DATE'), ('2000', 'DATE'), ('Cupertino', 'GPE'), ('CA', 'PRODUCT'), ('1.3', 'CARDINAL'), ('John Stickley Revised', 'PERSON'), ('SCE-API committee', 'ORG'), ('1.2', 'CARDINAL'), ('1.4', 'CARDINAL'), ('John Stickley', 'PERSON'), ('Susan RossIncorporated', 'PERSON'), ('SCE', 'ORG'), ('1', 'CARDINAL'), ('1.5 5-6-01', 'QUANTITY'), ('John Stickley Corrections', 'PERSON'), ('VHDL', 'ORG'), ('John Stickley Changes', 'PERSON'), ('feedback to 1.5', 'CARDINAL'), ('1.7', 'CARDINAL'), ('10-19-01', 'TIME'), ('John Stickley', 'PERSON'), ('ServiceLoop', 'ORG'), ('1.8', 'CARDINAL'), ('11-14-01', 'DATE'), ('John Stickley Incorporated', 'PERSON'), ('2', 'CARDINAL'), ('John Stickley Added', 'PERSON'), ('SceMiIC', 'ORG'), ('4', 'CARDINAL'), ('94', 'CARDINAL'), ('SCE', 'ORG'), ('Verilog', 'PRODUCT'), ('RTC', 'ORG'), ('UTC', 'ORG'), ('1.5', 'CARDINAL'), ('2.0 - Synopsys, Inc.', 'ORG'), ('CoWare, Inc.', 'ORG'), ('Frontier Design, Inc.', 'ORG'), ('2', 'CARDINAL'), ('3', 'CARDINAL'), ('the Verilog Hardware Description \nLanguage', 'FAC'), ('1364-1995', 'DATE'), ('4', 'CARDINAL'), ('IEEE Std', 'ORG'), ('1076-1993', 'DATE'), ('DUT', 'ORG'), ('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('SystemC', 'CARDINAL'), ('RTL', 'ORG'), ('API', 'ORG'), ('\x7fIt', 'PERSON'), ('\x7fIt', 'PERSON'), ('SystemC', 'CARDINAL'), ('SystemC', 'CARDINAL'), ('RTL', 'ORG'), ('SCE-MI', 'ORG'), ('5', 'CARDINAL'), ('941.6.1', 'CARDINAL'), ('C/C++', 'ORG'), ('1', 'CARDINAL'), ('DUT', 'ORG'), ('HDL', 'ORG'), ('HDL', 'ORG'), ('HDL', 'ORG'), ('dozens to hundreds', 'CARDINAL'), ('thousands', 'CARDINAL'), ('three', 'CARDINAL'), ('2.0', 'CARDINAL'), ('the SCE Modeling Interface', 'ORG'), ('SCE-MI', 'ORG'), ('3.0', 'CARDINAL'), ('4.0', 'CARDINAL'), ('API', 'ORG'), ('1.6.3 Document Conventions', 'MONEY'), ('API', 'ORG'), ('6', 'CARDINAL'), ('94', 'CARDINAL'), ('SCE', 'ORG'), ('1', 'CARDINAL'), ('SCE-MI', 'ORG'), ('DUT', 'ORG'), ('1', 'CARDINAL'), ('RTL', 'ORG'), ('RTL', 'ORG'), ('HDL', 'ORG'), ('SCE', 'ORG'), ('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('C++', 'NORP'), ('API', 'ORG'), ('DUT', 'ORG'), ('DUT', 'ORG'), ('DUT\n C/', 'ORG'), ('Hardware Side', 'PRODUCT'), ('emulator)SCE-MI InfrastructureMessage Port \nProxy 1', 'ORG'), ('2', 'CARDINAL'), ('SCE-MI', 'ORG'), ('7', 'CARDINAL'), ('94In', 'CARDINAL'), ('SCE', 'ORG'), ('2.1.1', 'CARDINAL'), ('SystemC', 'CARDINAL'), ('68', 'CARDINAL'), ('SCE', 'ORG'), ('CPU', 'ORG'), ('SCE', 'ORG'), ('2.2 Users', 'PERSON'), ('Interface', 'ORG'), ('three', 'CARDINAL'), ('\x7fSCE-MI', 'ORG'), ('2.2.1', 'CARDINAL'), ('RTL', 'ORG'), ('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('SCE-MI API', 'ORG'), ('DUT', 'ORG'), ('SCE', 'ORG'), ('section 4.1', 'LAW'), ('46', 'CARDINAL'), ('SceMiClockPort', 'ORG'), ('SCE', 'ORG'), ('94', 'CARDINAL'), ('SCE', 'ORG'), ('SCE', 'ORG'), ('IP', 'ORG'), ('only two', 'CARDINAL'), ('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('SystemC', 'CARDINAL'), ('2.2.3', 'CARDINAL'), ('SCE-MI Infrastructure', 'ORG'), ('2.3', 'CARDINAL'), ('Bridging Levels of Modeling Abstraction', 'ORG'), ('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('2.3.1', 'CARDINAL'), ('Untimed Software Level Modeling Abstraction\nSuppose', 'ORG'), ('DUT', 'ORG'), ('2', 'CARDINAL'), ('DUT', 'ORG'), ('USB', 'ORG'), ('DUT', 'ORG'), ('2', 'CARDINAL'), ('SystemC', 'CARDINAL'), ('SCE-MI', 'ORG'), ('9', 'CARDINAL'), ('94FIGURE 2', 'CARDINAL'), ('Software Testbench', 'PERSON'), ('DUT', 'ORG'), ('RTL', 'ORG'), ('DUT', 'ORG'), ('BCA', 'ORG'), ('2.3.2', 'CARDINAL'), ('Cycle Accurate Hardware Level Modeling Abstraction\nSuppose', 'ORG'), ('2', 'CARDINAL'), ('DUT', 'ORG'), ('3', 'CARDINAL'), ('DUT', 'ORG'), ('SCE-MI', 'ORG'), ('SCE', 'ORG'), ('TB Model 0', 'PRODUCT'), ('TB', 'ORG'), ('Model 1 TB Model N-1DUT ModelOverall Description', 'PRODUCT'), ('94', 'CARDINAL'), ('SCE-MI)arriving', 'ORG'), ('DUT', 'ORG'), ('DUT', 'ORG'), ('2', 'CARDINAL'), ('DUT', 'ORG'), ('DUT', 'ORG'), ('SCE', 'ORG'), ('7', 'CARDINAL'), ('DUT', 'ORG'), ('3', 'CARDINAL'), ('SCE', 'ORG'), ('SCE-MI', 'ORG'), ('11', 'CARDINAL'), ('94FIGURE 3', 'CARDINAL'), ('Multichannel Abstraction Bridge Architecture', 'ORG'), ('2.3.3', 'CARDINAL'), ('Transactions', 'PERSON'), ('RTL', 'ORG'), ('BCA)Message Input\nPort Proxy', 'PERSON'), ('0', 'CARDINAL'), ('Model 0', 'PRODUCT'), ('Model 1 TB Model N-1Message Output\nPort Proxy', 'PRODUCT'), ('1', 'CARDINAL'), ('ProxyHardware Side Software SideOverall Description', 'ORG'), ('12', 'CARDINAL'), ('94', 'CARDINAL'), ('SCE-MI)In', 'ORG'), ('C++', 'NORP'), ('2', 'CARDINAL'), ('1', 'CARDINAL'), ('SCE', 'ORG'), ('DUT', 'ORG'), ('DUT', 'ORG'), ('C++', 'NORP'), ('SystemC', 'CARDINAL'), ('DUT', 'ORG'), ('hundreds', 'CARDINAL'), ('DUT', 'ORG'), ('hundreds to thousands', 'CARDINAL'), ('DUT', 'ORG'), ('2.3.4', 'CARDINAL'), ('Controlled', 'NORP'), ('DUT', 'ORG'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('4', 'CARDINAL'), ('4', 'CARDINAL'), ('DUT', 'ORG'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('SCE-MI', 'ORG'), ('13', 'CARDINAL'), ('94FIGURE 4', 'CARDINAL'), ('SCE', 'ORG'), ('SCE', 'ORG'), ('DUT', 'ORG'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('SCE', 'ORG'), ('Time View', 'ORG'), ('94', 'CARDINAL'), ('four', 'CARDINAL'), ('2.4.1', 'CARDINAL'), ('third', 'ORDINAL'), ('IP', 'ORG'), ('ISS', 'ORG'), ('SCE', 'ORG'), ('2.4.2', 'CARDINAL'), ('DUT', 'ORG'), ('SCE', 'ORG'), ('SCE', 'ORG'), ('SCE', 'ORG'), ('2.4.3', 'CARDINAL'), ('2.4.4', 'CARDINAL'), ('API', 'ORG'), ('SCE-MI', 'ORG'), ('15', 'CARDINAL'), ('2.5', 'CARDINAL'), ('SCE-MI Interface Components', 'ORG'), ('2.5.1', 'CARDINAL'), ('Hardware Side Interface Components', 'ORG'), ('SCE', 'ORG'), ('SCE', 'ORG'), ('DUT', 'ORG'), ('Verilog', 'PRODUCT'), ('VHDL', 'PERSON'), ('API', 'ORG'), ('API', 'ORG'), ('RTC', 'ORG'), ('VHDL', 'PERSON'), ('RTC', 'ORG'), ('four', 'CARDINAL'), ('DUT', 'ORG'), ('2.5.2', 'CARDINAL'), ('Software', 'ORG'), ('Interface Components', 'ORG'), ('SCE-MI', 'ORG'), ('C++', 'NORP'), ('C++', 'NORP'), ('User’s Guide', 'ORG'), ('16', 'CARDINAL'), ('94', 'CARDINAL'), ('SCE', 'ORG'), ('3.1', 'CARDINAL'), ('SCE', 'ORG'), ('SCE', 'ORG'), ('SCE', 'ORG'), ('four', 'CARDINAL'), ('DUT', 'ORG'), ('One', 'CARDINAL'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('SceMiMessageOutPort', 'ORG'), ('SceMiClockPort', 'ORG'), ('SceMiClockPort', 'ORG'), ('SceMiClockPort', 'ORG'), ('DUT', 'ORG'), ('SceMiClockPort', 'ORG'), ('ClockNum', 'ORG'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('ClockNum', 'ORG'), ('SceMiClockPort', 'ORG'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('SCE', 'ORG'), ('SCE', 'ORG'), ('59', 'CARDINAL'), ('5', 'CARDINAL'), ('DUT', 'ORG'), ('SCE', 'ORG'), ('Tutorial\nFunctional Requirements Specification: Standard Co-Emulation Modeling Interface', 'ORG'), ('SCE-MI', 'ORG'), ('17', 'CARDINAL'), ('94FIGURE 5', 'DATE'), ('SCE', 'ORG'), ('DUT', 'ORG'), ('DUT', 'ORG'), ('SceMiMessageOutPort', 'ORG'), ('SceMiClockPort', 'ORG'), ('2.2', 'CARDINAL'), ('7', 'CARDINAL'), ('SCE', 'ORG'), ('SceMiClockPort', 'ORG'), ('SceMiClockPort', 'ORG'), ('SceMiClockPort', 'ORG'), ('5', 'CARDINAL'), ('1', 'CARDINAL'), ('1', 'CARDINAL'), ('1', 'DATE'), ('50', 'DATE'), ('50', 'DATE'), ('0', 'CARDINAL'), ('8)', 'CARDINAL'), ('SceMiClockPort', 'ORG'), ('4.1.4', 'CARDINAL'), ('51', 'CARDINAL'), ('1', 'CARDINAL'), ('1', 'CARDINAL'), ('1TransmitReady', 'CARDINAL'), ('63:0', 'CARDINAL'), ('MessageOut', 'ORG'), ('127:0]TransactorCore', 'CARDINAL'), ('DutInCtrl', 'PERSON'), ('DutInCtrl', 'PERSON'), ('1', 'CARDINAL'), ('1', 'DATE'), ('50', 'DATE'), ('50', 'DATE'), ('0', 'DATE'), ('8)', 'CARDINAL'), ('18', 'CARDINAL'), ('94', 'CARDINAL'), ('SCE-MI)\x7fDutyHi  =', 'ORG'), ('50', 'CARDINAL'), ('50', 'CARDINAL'), ('0', 'CARDINAL'), ('8', 'CARDINAL'), ('ClockNum', 'ORG'), ('1', 'CARDINAL'), ('ClockNum', 'ORG'), ('1', 'CARDINAL'), ('SceMiClockPort', 'ORG'), ('PortWidth', 'ORG'), ('Bridge', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('1/1', 'CARDINAL'), ('50/50', 'CARDINAL'), ('0', 'CARDINAL'), ('4.1.4.1', 'CARDINAL'), ('52', 'CARDINAL'), ('8', 'CARDINAL'), ('64', 'CARDINAL'), ('SceMiMessageOutPort', 'ORG'), ('128', 'CARDINAL'), ('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('three', 'CARDINAL'), ('Appendix', 'NORP'), ('90', 'CARDINAL'), ('3.2', 'CARDINAL'), ('SystemC', 'CARDINAL'), ('DUT', 'ORG'), ('Verilog', 'PRODUCT'), ('SystemC', 'CARDINAL'), ('SystemC', 'CARDINAL'), ('1', 'CARDINAL'), ('3.2.1', 'CARDINAL'), ('Origin', 'GPE'), ('Pipe s', 'PERSON'), ('Hubs', 'ORG'), ('RouteMap', 'GPE'), ('the \nOrigin s and', 'ORG'), ('Destination', 'PRODUCT'), ('RouteMap', 'ORG'), ('DUT', 'ORG'), ('SceMiMessageOutPort', 'ORG'), ('Destination', 'PRODUCT'), ('User’s Guide', 'ORG'), ('Tutorial\nFunctional Requirements Specification: Standard Co-Emulation Modeling Interface', 'ORG'), ('SCE-MI', 'ORG'), ('19', 'CARDINAL'), ('Anchorage', 'GPE'), ('Cupertino', 'GPE'), ('Noida', 'GPE'), ('SealBeach', 'ORG'), ('UK', 'GPE'), ('Waltham', 'GPE'), ('Anchorage', 'GPE'), ('Cupertino', 'GPE'), ('Maui', 'LOC'), ('SealBeach', 'ORG'), ('UK', 'GPE'), ('Origin', 'PERSON'), ('Destination', 'PRODUCT'), ('RouteMap', 'ORG'), ('DUT', 'ORG'), ('Pipe', 'ORG'), ('Hubs', 'PERSON'), ('Chicago', 'GPE'), ('Dallas', 'GPE'), ('Newark', 'GPE'), ('SanFran', 'GPE'), ('Seattle', 'GPE'), ('one hour', 'TIME'), ('6', 'CARDINAL'), ('User’s Guide', 'ORG'), ('94', 'CARDINAL'), ('SCE', 'ORG'), ('6', 'CARDINAL'), ('hours', 'TIME'), ('Pipe', 'ORG'), ('two hours', 'TIME'), ('RouteMap', 'ORG'), ('TeachRoute', 'ORG'), ('Waltham Origin', 'ORG'), ('TeachRoute', 'ORG'), ('5', 'CARDINAL'), ('Seattle', 'GPE'), ('1', 'CARDINAL'), ('3', 'CARDINAL'), ('Newark', 'GPE'), ('31Waltham', 'CARDINAL'), ('UK', 'GPE'), ('Tutorial\nFunctional Requirements Specification: Standard Co-Emulation Modeling Interface', 'ORG'), ('SCE-MI', 'ORG'), ('21', 'CARDINAL'), ('94addressed', 'CARDINAL'), ('Hub', 'ORG'), ('9', 'CARDINAL'), ('25', 'CARDINAL'), ('RouteConfig', 'ORG'), ('Waltham', 'GPE'), ('TeachRoute', 'ORG'), ('Hubs', 'PERSON'), ('Waltham', 'GPE'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('closer hubs', 'PERSON'), ('RouteMap', 'GPE'), ('4', 'CARDINAL'), ('22 days', 'DATE'), ('Destination', 'PRODUCT'), ('Origin', 'PRODUCT'), ('RouteMap', 'ORG'), ('3.2.2.1', 'CARDINAL'), ('TestbenchCalendar', 'ORG'), ('Calendar', 'PERSON'), ('Scheduler', 'ORG'), ('Origin', 'PERSON'), ('Destination', 'PRODUCT'), ('SCE-MI', 'ORG'), ('22', 'CARDINAL'), ('94', 'CARDINAL'), ('SCE', 'ORG'), ('Bridge', 'PERSON'), ('UK', 'GPE'), ('waltham\nDestination', 'ORG'), ('RouteMap                \nHub chicagoHub', 'PRODUCT'), ('Notice', 'ORG'), ('Bridge', 'ORG'), ('SceMiClockPort', 'ORG'), ('DUT', 'ORG'), ('SceMiMessageOutPort', 'ORG'), ('ClockAdvancer', 'ORG'), ('Hardware Side\n', 'PRODUCT'), ('7', 'CARDINAL'), ('3', 'CARDINAL'), ('11', 'CARDINAL'), ('13', 'CARDINAL'), ('Two', 'CARDINAL'), ('Calendar', 'PERSON'), ('six', 'CARDINAL'), ('Scheduler', 'PERSON'), ('five', 'CARDINAL'), ('Scheduler', 'PERSON'), ('User’s Guide', 'ORG'), ('Tutorial\nFunctional Requirements Specification: Standard Co-Emulation Modeling Interface', 'ORG'), ('SCE-MI', 'ORG'), ('23', 'CARDINAL'), ('94FIGURE 7', 'CARDINAL'), ('The Bridge\n', 'EVENT'), ('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('Calendar', 'PERSON'), ('Scheduler', 'PERSON'), ('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('SCE', 'ORG'), ('SystemC', 'CARDINAL'), ('Scheduler', 'PERSON'), ('DUT', 'ORG'), ('UK', 'GPE'), ('OrigDest', 'FAC'), ('Port', 'GPE'), ('ScheduleLeg', 'ORG'), ('PortNoida', 'ORG'), ('UK', 'GPE'), ('OrigDestRouteMapDUT\nMessageUser’s Guide and Tutorial\n24', 'ORG'), ('94', 'CARDINAL'), ('SCE-MI)In', 'ORG'), ('ClockAdvancer', 'ORG'), ('Calendar', 'PERSON'), ('ClockAdvancer', 'ORG'), ('DUT', 'ORG'), ('section 3.2.3.5', 'LAW'), ('28', 'CARDINAL'), ('DUT', 'ORG'), ('8', 'CARDINAL'), ('RouteMap', 'ORG'), ('DUT', 'ORG'), ('RouteMap', 'ORG'), ('8', 'CARDINAL'), ('DUT', 'ORG'), ('Transactor Interconnect\nOrigin\nTokenOut\nDestination\nTokenIn\nDestination\nTokenInP', 'ORG'), ('ePipe 5\nP\nip\n', 'PRODUCT'), ('ePipe 5\nP\nip\n', 'PRODUCT'), ('ePipe 4Funnel\nIn0', 'QUANTITY'), ('5AnchorageSeattle', 'CARDINAL'), ('Maui4User’s Guide', 'ORG'), ('Tutorial\nFunctional Requirements Specification: Standard Co-Emulation Modeling Interface', 'ORG'), ('SCE-MI', 'ORG'), ('25', 'CARDINAL'), ('94Pipe', 'CARDINAL'), ('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('Destination', 'PRODUCT'), ('Longer Pipe', 'ORG'), ('one hour Pipe', 'TIME'), ('one hour', 'TIME'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('the Seattle Hub  and', 'FAC'), ('Maui Destination', 'ORG'), ('four hour', 'TIME'), ('Seattle', 'GPE'), ('3.2.3.3', 'CARDINAL'), ('DUT', 'ORG'), ('Transactor Components', 'ORG'), ('9', 'CARDINAL'), ('DUT', 'ORG'), ('9', 'CARDINAL'), ('DUT', 'ORG'), ('Transactor Components', 'ORG'), ('MessageIn Port\nClockControl', 'PERSON'), ('MessageOut Port\nClockControl\nMessageIn Port', 'ORG'), ('PortOrigin', 'PRODUCT'), ('TokenOut1', 'DATE'), ('TokenOut', 'ORG'), ('32', 'CARDINAL'), ('32', 'CARDINAL'), ('32', 'CARDINAL'), ('32', 'CARDINAL'), ('32', 'CARDINAL'), ('32', 'CARDINAL'), ('0307 1113', 'DATE'), ('Token', 'PERSON'), ('1115', 'DATE'), ('23 31', 'DATE'), ('31Token', 'CARDINAL'), ('26', 'CARDINAL'), ('94', 'CARDINAL'), ('SCE-MI)Each Origin', 'ORG'), ('Scheduler', 'PERSON'), ('TokenOut', 'ORG'), ('Origin', 'PRODUCT'), ('Scheduler', 'PERSON'), ('RouteMap', 'ORG'), ('Destination', 'PRODUCT'), ('TokenIn', 'PERSON'), ('3.2.3.4', 'CARDINAL'), ('26', 'CARDINAL'), ('Destination', 'PRODUCT'), ('32', 'CARDINAL'), ('0s', 'DATE'), ('Token', 'ORG'), ('9', 'CARDINAL'), ('Destination', 'PRODUCT'), ('Funnel', 'ORG'), ('up to four', 'CARDINAL'), ('Nozzle', 'PERSON'), ('four', 'CARDINAL'), ('Nozzle', 'PERSON'), ('TeachRoute', 'ORG'), ('3.2.3.4', 'CARDINAL'), ('DUT', 'ORG'), ('Clock', 'ORG'), ('RouteMap', 'ORG'), ('Destination', 'PRODUCT'), ('RouteMap', 'ORG'), ('TokenIn', 'PERSON'), ('RouteMap', 'ORG'), ('Verilog', 'PERSON'), ('Destination', 'PRODUCT'), ('User’s Guide', 'ORG'), ('Tutorial\nFunctional Requirements Specification: Standard Co-Emulation Modeling Interface', 'ORG'), ('SCE-MI', 'ORG'), ('27', 'CARDINAL'), ('3:0', 'CARDINAL'), ('31:0', 'CARDINAL'), ('1', 'CARDINAL'), ('1', 'CARDINAL'), ('0', 'CARDINAL'), ('0', 'CARDINAL'), ('DUT', 'ORG'), ('DUT', 'ORG'), ('0', 'CARDINAL'), ('DUT', 'ORG'), ('1', 'CARDINAL'), ('0', 'CARDINAL'), ('&& destID', 'ORG'), ('0', 'CARDINAL'), ('1', 'CARDINAL'), ('DUT', 'ORG'), ('0', 'CARDINAL'), ('0', 'CARDINAL'), ('User’s Guide', 'ORG'), ('28', 'CARDINAL'), ('94', 'CARDINAL'), ('ClockAdvancer', 'ORG'), ('ClockAdvancer', 'ORG'), ('User’s Guide', 'ORG'), ('Tutorial\nFunctional Requirements Specification: Standard Co-Emulation Modeling Interface', 'ORG'), ('SCE-MI', 'ORG'), ('29', 'CARDINAL'), ('Verilog', 'PRODUCT'), ('ClockAdvancer', 'ORG'), ('ClockAdvancer', 'ORG'), ('31:0', 'CARDINAL'), ('31:0', 'CARDINAL'), ('1', 'CARDINAL'), ('messageIn[31:0', 'CARDINAL'), ('0', 'CARDINAL'), ('0', 'CARDINAL'), ('0', 'CARDINAL'), ('0', 'CARDINAL'), ('transmitReadyIn && !', 'ORG'), ('1', 'CARDINAL'), ('1', 'CARDINAL'), ('readyForCclock && cclockEnabled', 'ORG'), ('1', 'CARDINAL'), ('1', 'CARDINAL'), ('0', 'CARDINAL'), ('1', 'CARDINAL'), ('0', 'CARDINAL'), ('Notice', 'ORG'), ('Destination', 'PRODUCT'), ('ClockAdvancer', 'ORG'), ('the Destination  User’s Guide', 'ORG'), ('30', 'CARDINAL'), ('94', 'CARDINAL'), ('SCE', 'ORG'), ('only one', 'CARDINAL'), ('1/1', 'CARDINAL'), ('Notice', 'ORG'), ('ClockAdvancer', 'ORG'), ('0', 'CARDINAL'), ('ClockAdvancer', 'ORG'), ('4.3.5.3', 'CARDINAL'), ('75', 'CARDINAL'), ('3.2.4', 'CARDINAL'), ('Software', 'ORG'), ('Routed', 'NORP'), ('SystemC', 'GPE'), ('C++', 'PERSON'), ('SCE', 'ORG'), ('3.2.4.1', 'CARDINAL'), ('The\n System  Model: Interconnect of', 'ORG'), ('System', 'ORG'), ('SystemC modules', 'QUANTITY'), ('SC_MODULE', 'PERSON'), ('System', 'ORG'), ('10', 'CARDINAL'), ('10', 'CARDINAL'), ('SystemC', 'CARDINAL'), ('ScheduleLeg', 'ORG'), ('DoneCalendar', 'PRODUCT'), ('AdvanceCalendar', 'ORG'), ('DoneScheduler', 'ORG'), ('RouteConfig\nLoadRouteMap LoadRoute', 'ORG'), ('Channel sTestbench ArchitectureUser’s Guide', 'ORG'), ('Tutorial\nFunctional Requirements Specification: Standard Co-Emulation Modeling Interface', 'ORG'), ('SCE-MI', 'ORG'), ('31', 'CARDINAL'), ('System', 'PERSON'), ('SC_MODULE', 'PERSON'), ('Testbench      *', 'PERSON'), ('Calendar       ', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('Scheduler      *', 'PERSON'), ('RouteConfig    *', 'ORG'), ('Testbench', 'ORG'), ('testbench->NewDay(          newDay', 'DATE'), ('testbench->LoadRouteMap', 'PERSON'), ('Calendar', 'PERSON'), ('Scheduler', 'PERSON'), ('RouteConfig', 'ORG'), ('routeConfig->LoadRouteMap', 'ORG'), ('SystemC', 'CARDINAL'), ('User’s Guide', 'ORG'), ('32', 'CARDINAL'), ('94', 'CARDINAL'), ('SystemC', 'CARDINAL'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('SystemC', 'CARDINAL'), ('SCE', 'ORG'), ('SystemC', 'CARDINAL'), ('C++', 'NORP'), ('1', 'CARDINAL'), ('SystemC', 'CARDINAL'), ('SCE-MI', 'ORG'), ('SystemC', 'CARDINAL'), ('10', 'CARDINAL'), ('SystemC', 'CARDINAL'), ('Testbench', 'ORG'), ('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('Tutorial\nFunctional Requirements Specification: Standard Co-Emulation Modeling Interface', 'ORG'), ('SCE-MI', 'ORG'), ('33', 'CARDINAL'), ('943.2.4.2', 'CARDINAL'), ('Routine', 'ORG'), ('Error Handler', 'PERSON'), ('SystemC', 'CARDINAL'), ('C++', 'PERSON'), ('void errorHandler', 'PERSON'), ('ec', 'ORG'), ('SCE-MI Error', 'ORG'), ('\\n', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('errorHandler', 'PERSON'), ('NULL', 'ORG'), ('NULL', 'ORG'), ('1', 'CARDINAL'), ('// Instantiate', 'ORG'), ('system.calendar  ->Bind', 'PRODUCT'), ('SystemC', 'CARDINAL'), ('Fatal Error: Program', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('-1', 'ORG'), ('Fatal Error: Program', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('-1', 'ORG'), ('0', 'CARDINAL'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('errorHandler', 'PERSON'), ('User’s Guide', 'ORG'), ('34', 'CARDINAL'), ('94', 'CARDINAL'), ('SCE-MI)before', 'ORG'), ('C++', 'NORP'), ('SCE', 'ORG'), ('System', 'ORG'), ('SCE-MI', 'ORG'), ('Bind', 'PERSON'), ('SystemC', 'CARDINAL'), ('-1', 'ORG'), ('3.2.4.3', 'CARDINAL'), ('SCE-MI Service', 'ORG'), ('SCE', 'ORG'), ('68', 'CARDINAL'), ('SCE', 'ORG'), ('Tutorial\nFunctional Requirements Specification: Standard Co-Emulation Modeling Interface', 'ORG'), ('SCE-MI', 'ORG'), ('35', 'CARDINAL'), ('SC_MODULE', 'PERSON'), ('// Autonomous SceMi', 'PERSON'), ('Bind', 'ORG'), ('SC_CTOR', 'ORG'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('Testbench', 'GPE'), ('10', 'CARDINAL'), ('30', 'CARDINAL'), ('Done', 'ORG'), ('Testbench', 'ORG'), ('Testbench', 'ORG'), ('section).User’s Guide', 'ORG'), ('36', 'CARDINAL'), ('94', 'CARDINAL'), ('SCE-MI)3.2.4.4 Application Specific Data Types', 'ORG'), ('Routed.hxx', 'ORG'), ('NumPassengers', 'ORG'), ('4', 'CARDINAL'), ('NumLocations', 'ORG'), ('12', 'CARDINAL'), ('MessageSize', 'ORG'), ('15', 'CARDINAL'), ('BugsBunny', 'ORG'), ('ElmerFudd', 'ORG'), ('LocationIDs', 'PERSON'), ('1', 'CARDINAL'), ('2', 'CARDINAL'), ('Cupertino', 'GPE'), ('3', 'CARDINAL'), ('Dallas', 'GPE'), ('4', 'CARDINAL'), ('5', 'CARDINAL'), ('6', 'CARDINAL'), ('7', 'CARDINAL'), ('8', 'CARDINAL'), ('9', 'CARDINAL'), ('Seattle', 'GPE'), ('10', 'CARDINAL'), ('UK', 'GPE'), ('11', 'CARDINAL'), ('12', 'CARDINAL'), ('LocationIDs', 'PERSON'), ('LocationIDs', 'PERSON'), ('ArrivalRecord', 'ORG'), ('LayoverCount', 'ORG'), ('LocationIDs', 'PERSON'), ('OriginID', 'ORG'), ('LocationIDs', 'PERSON'), ('LocationIDs', 'PERSON'), ('Route', 'ORG'), ('LocationIDs', 'PERSON'), ('LocationIDs', 'PERSON'), ('Date', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('Tutorial\nFunctional Requirements Specification: Standard Co-Emulation Modeling Interface', 'ORG'), ('SCE-MI', 'ORG'), ('37', 'CARDINAL'), ('94', 'CARDINAL'), ('3.2.4.5', 'CARDINAL'), ('Testbench', 'ORG'), ('SystemC', 'CARDINAL'), ('four', 'CARDINAL'), ('Scheduler', 'PERSON'), ('Testbench', 'ORG'), ('day', 'DATE'), ('BugsBunny', 'ORG'), ('20', 'CARDINAL'), ('10', 'CARDINAL'), ('BugsBunny', 'ORG'), ('BugsBunny', 'ORG'), ('day', 'DATE'), ('DaffyDuck', 'ORG'), ('Waltham', 'GPE'), ('Cupertino', 'GPE'), ('DaffyDuck', 'ORG'), ('Cupertino', 'GPE'), ('22', 'CARDINAL'), ('DaffyDuck', 'ORG'), ('Cupertino', 'GPE'), ('DaffyDuck', 'ORG'), ('day', 'DATE'), ('3,      5', 'TIME'), ('ElmerFudd', 'ORG'), ('23', 'CARDINAL'), ('3', 'CARDINAL'), ('ElmerFudd', 'ORG'), ('Cupertino', 'GPE'), ('ElmerFudd', 'ORG'), ('/*On day', 'DATE'), ('1,      1', 'TIME'), ('20', 'CARDINAL'), ('BugsBunny      ', 'PRODUCT'), ('Chicago', 'GPE'), ('Cupertino', 'GPE'), ('Dallas', 'GPE'), ('Maui     ', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('SanFran', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('SealBeach', 'ORG'), ('Seattle', 'GPE'), ('UK', 'GPE'), ('User’s Guide', 'ORG'), ('38', 'CARDINAL'), ('94', 'CARDINAL'), ('four', 'CARDINAL'), ('SystemC', 'CARDINAL'), ('SC_MODULE', 'PERSON'), ('Testbench', 'ORG'), ('SystemC', 'CARDINAL'), ('SC_CTOR', 'ORG'), ('SC_MODULE', 'PERSON'), ('Testbench', 'ORG'), ('sc_master', 'PERSON'), ('sc_master', 'PERSON'), ('NewDay', 'CARDINAL'), ('ScheduleLeg', 'ORG'), ('// Autonomous', 'PERSON'), ('NewDay', 'CARDINAL'), ('Testbench', 'ORG'), ('SC_THREAD', 'ORG'), ('NewDay', 'CARDINAL'), ('User’s Guide', 'ORG'), ('Tutorial\nFunctional Requirements Specification: Standard Co-Emulation Modeling Interface', 'ORG'), ('SCE-MI', 'ORG'), ('39', 'CARDINAL'), ('// Signal RouteConfig', 'PERSON'), ('RouteMap', 'ORG'), ('AdvanceCalendar', 'ORG'), ('1', 'CARDINAL'), ('// Advance', 'PERSON'), ('day 1', 'DATE'), ('// Wait', 'PERSON'), ('1000', 'CARDINAL'), ('today', 'DATE'), ('tomorrow', 'DATE'), ('tomorrow', 'DATE'), ('dItineraries[i]->DateOfTravel', 'CARDINAL'), ('00', 'CARDINAL'), ('ScheduleLeg', 'ORG'), ('AdvanceCalendar', 'PRODUCT'), ('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('First', 'ORDINAL'), ('LoadRouteMap', 'GPE'), ('RouteConfig', 'ORG'), ('Hubs', 'ORG'), ('RouteMap', 'GPE'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('RouteConfig', 'ORG'), ('AdvanceClock', 'ORG'), ('Calendar', 'PERSON'), ('RouteMap', 'ORG'), ('Hubs', 'ORG'), ('RouteMap', 'ORG'), ('Calendar', 'PERSON'), ('Calendar', 'PERSON'), ('NewDay', 'CARDINAL'), ('the current day', 'DATE'), ('Calendar', 'PERSON'), ('the first day', 'DATE'), ('ScheduleLeg', 'ORG'), ('Scheduler', 'PERSON'), ('User’s Guide', 'ORG'), ('94', 'CARDINAL'), ('SCE', 'ORG'), ('the Maui  Destination', 'FAC'), ('Testbench', 'ORG'), ('ArrivalRecord', 'ORG'), ('Scheduler', 'PERSON'), ('00', 'CARDINAL'), ('\\n        ', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('= Routed::Maui &&', 'ORG'), ('Maui', 'LOC'), ('// Signal', 'PERSON'), ('User’s Guide', 'ORG'), ('Tutorial\nFunctional Requirements Specification: Standard Co-Emulation Modeling Interface', 'ORG'), ('SCE-MI', 'ORG'), ('41', 'CARDINAL'), ('943.2.4.6', 'CARDINAL'), ('SystemC', 'CARDINAL'), ('Scheduler', 'PERSON'), ('SC_MODULE', 'PERSON'), ('Scheduler', 'PERSON'), ('ScheduleLeg', 'ORG'), ('SceMiMessageData', 'ORG'), ('Bind', 'ORG'), ('SC_CTOR', 'ORG'), ('Scheduler', 'ORG'), ('dOriginAnchorage(NULL', 'ORG'), ('dOriginWaltham(NULL', 'PERSON'), ('dDestinationAnchorage(NULL', 'GPE'), ('ScheduleLeg', 'ORG'), ('LoadRoute', 'ORG'), ('User’s Guide', 'ORG'), ('94', 'CARDINAL'), ('SCE-MI', 'ORG'), ('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('TeachRoute', 'ORG'), ('RouteMap', 'ORG'), ('the Waltham Origin', 'ORG'), ('RouteMap', 'ORG'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('RouteConfig', 'ORG'), ('LoadRouteMap', 'GPE'), ('Scheduler', 'PERSON'), ('ScheduleLeg', 'ORG'), ('Testbench', 'ORG'), ('Origin', 'PRODUCT'), ('Scheduler', 'PERSON'), ('Origin', 'PRODUCT'), ('ScheduleLeg', 'ORG'), ('4', 'CARDINAL'), ('12', 'CARDINAL'), ('16', 'CARDINAL'), ('0', 'CARDINAL'), ('3.2.4.2', 'CARDINAL'), ('33', 'CARDINAL'), ('SCE', 'ORG'), ('User’s Guide', 'ORG'), ('Tutorial\nFunctional Requirements Specification: Standard Co-Emulation Modeling Interface', 'ORG'), ('SCE-MI', 'ORG'), ('43', 'CARDINAL'), ('4.3.3.5', 'CARDINAL'), ('67', 'CARDINAL'), ('TokenIn', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('TokenIn', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('TokenIn', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('TokenIn', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('TokenIn', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('TokenIn', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('TokenOut', 'ORG'), ('= scemi->BindMessageOutPort', 'PERSON'), ('TokenOut', 'ORG'), ('dDestinationMaui      ', 'PRODUCT'), ('TokenOut', 'ORG'), ('TokenOut', 'ORG'), ('TokenOut', 'ORG'), ('Scheduler', 'PERSON'), ('Calendar', 'PERSON'), ('24 hours', 'TIME'), ('24', 'CARDINAL'), ('Scheduler', 'ORG'), ('SCE', 'ORG'), ('Bind', 'PERSON'), ('SceMiMessageData', 'ORG'), ('Scheduler', 'PERSON'), ('Routed::ArrivalRecord', 'CARDINAL'), ('TodaysDate', 'ORG'), ('Calendar', 'PERSON'), ('User’s Guide', 'ORG'), ('94', 'CARDINAL'), ('SCE', 'ORG'), ('Testbench', 'ORG'), ('TodaysDate', 'ORG'), ('today', 'DATE'), ('Calendar', 'PERSON'), ('todaysDate.', 'DATE'), ('Routed::PassengerIDs', 'ORG'), ('Routed::LocationIDs', 'ORG'), ('4', 'CARDINAL'), ('Routed::LocationIDs', 'ORG'), ('12', 'CARDINAL'), ('LayoverCount', 'ORG'), ('8)', 'CARDINAL'), ('LayoverCount', 'ORG'), ('5', 'CARDINAL'), ('16', 'CARDINAL'), ('LayoverCount', 'ORG'), ('Routed::LocationIDs', 'ORG'), ('arrivalToken & 0xf', 'ORG'), ('4', 'CARDINAL'), ('// Arrival', 'PERSON'), ('3.2.4.7', 'CARDINAL'), ('Calendar', 'PERSON'), ('RouteMap', 'ORG'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('Origin', 'PRODUCT'), ('a particular day', 'DATE'), ('Calendar', 'PERSON'), ('DUT', 'ORG'), ('24', 'CARDINAL'), ('24 hours', 'TIME'), ('24', 'CARDINAL'), ('more than one day', 'DATE'), ('Calendar', 'PERSON'), ('ClockAdvancer', 'ORG'), ('DUT', 'ORG'), ('ClockControl', 'ORG'), ('Calendar', 'PRODUCT'), ('Scheduler', 'PERSON'), ('Calendar', 'PERSON'), ('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('AdvanceCalendar', 'ORG'), ('User’s Guide', 'ORG'), ('Tutorial\nFunctional Requirements Specification: Standard Co-Emulation Modeling Interface', 'ORG'), ('SCE-MI', 'ORG'), ('45', 'CARDINAL'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('RouteMap', 'ORG'), ('TeachRoute', 'ORG'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('0', 'CARDINAL'), ('1', 'CARDINAL'), ('1', 'CARDINAL'), ('// Send', 'PERSON'), ('Notice', 'ORG'), ('SystemC', 'CARDINAL'), ('SystemC', 'CARDINAL'), ('34', 'CARDINAL'), ('ClockAdvancer', 'ORG'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('SceMiMessageData', 'ORG'), ('Calendar', 'PERSON'), ('SceMiMessageData', 'ORG'), ('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('Formal Functional Specification', 'ORG'), ('46', 'CARDINAL'), ('94', 'CARDINAL'), ('Formal Functional Specification\n4.1', 'ORG'), ('4.1.1 Dual Ready Protocol', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('11', 'CARDINAL'), ('11', 'CARDINAL'), ('TransmitReady', 'PERSON'), ('ReceiveReady', 'PERSON'), ('ReceiveReady', 'PERSON'), ('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('TransmitReady', 'PERSON'), ('ReceiveReady', 'ORG'), ('d1 1st', 'DATE'), ('SCE-MI', 'ORG'), ('47', 'CARDINAL'), ('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('12', 'CARDINAL'), ('Verilog', 'PRODUCT'), ('VHDL', 'PERSON'), ('12', 'CARDINAL'), ('4.1.2.1', 'CARDINAL'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('11', 'CARDINAL'), ('46', 'CARDINAL'), ('48', 'CARDINAL'), ('ReceiveReady', 'ORG'), ('ReceiveReady', 'ORG'), ('ReceiveReady', 'NORP'), ('TransmitReady', 'PERSON'), ('PortWidth', 'ORG'), ('1', 'CARDINAL'), ('ReceiveReady', 'ORG'), ('PortWidth-1:0] Message', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('VHDL Macro Wrapper', 'ORG'), ('PortWidth', 'ORG'), ('ReceiveReady', 'NORP'), ('EmptyMacro', 'ORG'), ('48', 'CARDINAL'), ('94', 'CARDINAL'), ('SCE', 'ORG'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('TransmitReady', 'PERSON'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('ReceiveReady', 'ORG'), ('4.1.2.2 Input Ready Propagation', 'PERSON'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('section 4.3.3.4', 'LAW'), ('66', 'CARDINAL'), ('SCE', 'ORG'), ('ServiceLoop', 'ORG'), ('ServiceLoop', 'ORG'), ('second', 'ORDINAL'), ('ServiceLoop', 'ORG'), ('Formal Functional Specification\nFunctional Requirements Specification: Standard Co-Emulation Modeling Interface', 'ORG'), ('SCE-MI', 'ORG'), ('49', 'CARDINAL'), ('94It', 'CARDINAL'), ('ServiceLoop', 'ORG'), ('50', 'CARDINAL'), ("51'st", 'CARDINAL'), ('ServiceLoop', 'ORG'), ('11', 'CARDINAL'), ('46', 'CARDINAL'), ('First', 'ORDINAL'), ('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('Second', 'ORDINAL'), ('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('13', 'CARDINAL'), ('four', 'CARDINAL'), ('13', 'CARDINAL'), ('MessageFormal Functional Specification', 'ORG'), ('50', 'CARDINAL'), ('94', 'CARDINAL'), ('\x7fReceiveReady', 'PERSON'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('\x7fReceiveReady', 'PERSON'), ('0', 'CARDINAL'), ('1', 'CARDINAL'), ('\x7fReceiveReady', 'PERSON'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('ReceiveReady', 'ORG'), ('SceMiMessageOutPort', 'ORG'), ('SCE', 'ORG'), ('SceMiMessageOutPort', 'ORG'), ('14', 'CARDINAL'), ('SceMiMessageOutPort', 'ORG'), ('Verilog', 'PRODUCT'), ('VHDL', 'PERSON'), ('14', 'CARDINAL'), ('SceMiMessageOutPort', 'ORG'), ('Macro', 'ORG'), ('4.1.3.1 Parameters and', 'ORG'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('more than one', 'CARDINAL'), ('59', 'CARDINAL'), ('SceMiMessageOutPort', 'ORG'), ('ReceiveReady', 'NORP'), ('PortWidth', 'ORG'), ('1', 'CARDINAL'), ('PortPriority', 'ORG'), ('10', 'CARDINAL'), ('ReceiveReady', 'NORP'), ('VHDL Macro Wrapper', 'ORG'), ('SceMiMessageOutPort', 'ORG'), ('PortWidth', 'ORG'), ('PortPriority', 'ORG'), ('10', 'CARDINAL'), ('EmptyMacro', 'ORG'), ('SceMiMessageOutPort', 'ORG'), ('Functional Specification\nFunctional Requirements Specification: Standard Co-Emulation Modeling Interface', 'ORG'), ('SCE-MI', 'ORG'), ('51', 'CARDINAL'), ('94TransmitReady', 'CARDINAL'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('ReceiveReady  ', 'PERSON'), ('TransmitReady', 'PERSON'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('ReceiveReady', 'ORG'), ('TransmitReady', 'PERSON'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('SCE', 'ORG'), ('ReceiveReady', 'PERSON'), ('section 4.3.7.1', 'LAW'), ('77', 'CARDINAL'), ('SceMiClockPort', 'ORG'), ('DUT', 'ORG'), ('SceMiClockPort', 'ORG'), ('SceMiClockPort', 'ORG'), ('SceMiClockPort', 'ORG'), ('15', 'CARDINAL'), ('SceMiClockPort', 'ORG'), ('Verilog', 'PRODUCT'), ('VHDL', 'PERSON'), ('Formal Functional Specification\n52', 'ORG'), ('94', 'CARDINAL'), ('SCE', 'ORG'), ('15', 'CARDINAL'), ('SceMiClockPort Macro\nNote', 'ORG'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('SceMiClockPort', 'ORG'), ('1/1', 'CARDINAL'), ('54', 'CARDINAL'), ('0', 'CARDINAL'), ('SCE', 'ORG'), ('1/1', 'CARDINAL'), ('SceMiClockPort', 'ORG'), ('1/1', 'CARDINAL'), ('SceMiClockPort', 'ORG'), ('1/1', 'CARDINAL'), ('4/1', 'CARDINAL'), ('4', 'CARDINAL'), ('1/1', 'CARDINAL'), ('only 1', 'CARDINAL'), ('4.1.4.1', 'CARDINAL'), ('SceMiClockPort', 'ORG'), ('more than one', 'CARDINAL'), ('SceMiClockPort', 'ORG'), ('ClockNum', 'ORG'), ('ClockNum', 'ORG'), ('SceMiClockPort', 'ORG'), ('ClockNum=1', 'GPE'), ('DutyHi=0', 'PRODUCT'), ('VHDL Macro Wrapper', 'ORG'), ('SceMiClockPort', 'ORG'), ('ClockNum', 'ORG'), ('1', 'CARDINAL'), ('1', 'CARDINAL'), ('1', 'CARDINAL'), ('0', 'CARDINAL'), ('100', 'CARDINAL'), ('0', 'CARDINAL'), ('8', 'CARDINAL'), ('EmptyMacro', 'ORG'), ('SceMiClockPort', 'ORG'), ('Functional Specification\nFunctional Requirements Specification: Standard Co-Emulation Modeling Interface', 'ORG'), ('SCE-MI', 'ORG'), ('53', 'CARDINAL'), ('94RatioNumerator=1', 'CARDINAL'), ('1/1', 'CARDINAL'), ('5/2', 'CARDINAL'), ('5', 'CARDINAL'), ('1/1', 'CARDINAL'), ('only 2', 'CARDINAL'), ('1/1', 'CARDINAL'), ('DutyHi=0, DutyLo=100', 'ORG'), ('75', 'CARDINAL'), ('100', 'CARDINAL'), ('75%', 'PERCENT'), ('25%', 'PERCENT'), ('30%', 'PERCENT'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('15', 'CARDINAL'), ('100', 'CARDINAL'), ('section 4.1.4.3', 'LAW'), ('54', 'CARDINAL'), ('1', 'CARDINAL'), ('0', 'CARDINAL'), ('DUT', 'ORG'), ('SCE', 'ORG'), ('DUT', 'ORG'), ('SCE', 'ORG'), ('4.1.4.2 Deriving', 'ORG'), ('Clock Ratios', 'PERSON'), ('\x7fmake', 'GPE'), ('100Mhz', 'CARDINAL'), ('25Mhz', 'CARDINAL'), ('10Mhz', 'CARDINAL'), ('7.5', 'CARDINAL'), ('Mhz', 'NORP'), ('32kHz', 'CARDINAL'), ('100000 / 100000', 'DATE'), ('100000 / 25000100000', 'DATE'), ('94', 'CARDINAL'), ('SCE', 'ORG'), ('100000', 'DATE'), ('SCE', 'ORG'), ('4.1.4.3', 'CARDINAL'), ('15', 'CARDINAL'), ('0', 'CARDINAL'), ('DutyHi=0, DutyLo=100', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('100', 'CARDINAL'), ('0+100', 'CARDINAL'), ('30', 'CARDINAL'), ('30%', 'PERCENT'), ('DutyHi=3', 'NORP'), ('DutyLo=1', 'GPE'), ('75%/25%', 'PERCENT'), ('50%', 'PERCENT'), ('3', 'CARDINAL'), ('0', 'CARDINAL'), ('DutyLo=0', 'GPE'), ('SCE-MI', 'ORG'), ('55', 'CARDINAL'), ('944.1.4.4', 'CARDINAL'), ('Controlled Reset Semantics', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('SceMiClockPort', 'ORG'), ('ResetCycles', 'ORG'), ('SceMiClockPort', 'ORG'), ('Creset', 'ORG'), ('2', 'CARDINAL'), ('\x7fFor multiple cclocks', 'ORG'), ('max', 'PERSON'), ('section 4.1.4.5', 'DATE'), ('55', 'CARDINAL'), ('Creset', 'ORG'), ('SceMiClockPort', 'ORG'), ('SceMiClockPort', 'ORG'), ('4.1.4.5', 'CARDINAL'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('0', 'CARDINAL'), ('0', 'CARDINAL'), ('16', 'CARDINAL'), ('cclock1', 'ORG'), ('cclock2', 'GPE'), ('0', 'CARDINAL'), ('cclock4', 'ORG'), ('cclock2', 'ORG'), ('50%', 'PERCENT'), ('2 uclocks', 'QUANTITY'), ('1/2', 'CARDINAL'), ('0', 'CARDINAL'), ('50%', 'PERCENT'), ('1/2', 'CARDINAL'), ('1', 'CARDINAL'), ('1.Formal', 'CARDINAL'), ('Functional Specification\n56', 'ORG'), ('94', 'CARDINAL'), ('SCE', 'ORG'), ('16', 'CARDINAL'), ('Multi-Clock Alignment\n4.1.5SceMiClockControl  Macro', 'ORG'), ('SceMiClockPort', 'ORG'), ('at least one', 'CARDINAL'), ('DUT', 'ORG'), ('SCE', 'ORG'), ('17', 'CARDINAL'), ('Verilog', 'PRODUCT'), ('VHDL', 'PERSON'), ('2/1', 'CARDINAL'), ('50/50', 'CARDINAL'), ('0', 'CARDINAL'), ('2/1', 'CARDINAL'), ('25/75', 'CARDINAL'), ('0', 'CARDINAL'), ('2/1', 'CARDINAL'), ('75/25', 'CARDINAL'), ('0', 'CARDINAL'), ('2/1', 'CARDINAL'), ('25/75', 'CARDINAL'), ('50', 'CARDINAL'), ('2/1', 'CARDINAL'), ('75/25', 'CARDINAL'), ('50Formal Functional Specification\nFunctional Requirements Specification: Standard Co-Emulation Modeling Interface', 'ORG'), ('SCE-MI', 'ORG'), ('57', 'CARDINAL'), ('94FIGURE 17', 'DATE'), ('SceMiClockPort', 'ORG'), ('at least one', 'CARDINAL'), ('4.1.5.1', 'CARDINAL'), ('SceMiClockPort', 'ORG'), ('ClockNum', 'ORG'), ('1', 'CARDINAL'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('SceMiClockPort', 'ORG'), ('SceMiClockPort', 'ORG'), ('SceMiClockPort', 'ORG'), ('ClockNum', 'ORG'), ('SceMiClockPort', 'ORG'), ('SCE', 'ORG'), ('SCE', 'ORG'), ('Ureset', 'ORG'), ('CclockEnabled', 'PERSON'), ('ClockNum', 'ORG'), ('1', 'CARDINAL'), ('Uclock, Ureset', 'ORG'), ('CclockEnabled', 'ORG'), ('VHDL Macro Wrapper', 'ORG'), ('ClockNum', 'ORG'), ('1', 'CARDINAL'), ('EmptyMacro', 'ORG'), ('Functional Specification', 'ORG'), ('94', 'CARDINAL'), ('SceMiClockPort', 'ORG'), ('55', 'CARDINAL'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('SCE', 'ORG'), ('DUT', 'ORG'), ('DUT', 'ORG'), ('One', 'CARDINAL'), ('DUT', 'ORG'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('5', 'CARDINAL'), ('17', 'CARDINAL'), ('DUT', 'ORG'), ('SCE', 'ORG'), ('CclockEnabled', 'PERSON'), ('4.1.4.3', 'CARDINAL'), ('54', 'CARDINAL'), ('CclockEnabled', 'ORG'), ('CclockEnabled', 'ORG'), ('Formal Functional Specification\nFunctional Requirements Specification: Standard Co-Emulation Modeling Interface', 'ORG'), ('SCE-MI', 'ORG'), ('59', 'CARDINAL'), ('94Note', 'CARDINAL'), ('4.1.4.3', 'CARDINAL'), ('54', 'CARDINAL'), ('0', 'CARDINAL'), ('4.2', 'CARDINAL'), ('8', 'CARDINAL'), ('14', 'CARDINAL'), ('SCE', 'ORG'), ('at least one', 'CARDINAL'), ('Transactor Name', 'PERSON'), ('SceMiMessageOutPort', 'ORG'), ('Port Name', 'GPE'), ('Verilog', 'PRODUCT'), ('Bridge.u1.tx1', 'PERSON'), ('Formal Functional Specification\n60', 'ORG'), ('94', 'CARDINAL'), ('Message Input', 'PERSON'), ('Port Width', 'GPE'), ('PortWidth', 'ORG'), ('1', 'CARDINAL'), ('Message Output Port Priority', 'ORG'), ('PortPrority', 'ORG'), ('SceMiMessageOutPort', 'ORG'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('10', 'CARDINAL'), ('UNIX', 'ORG'), ('20', 'CARDINAL'), ('10', 'CARDINAL'), ('0', 'CARDINAL'), ('SceMiClockPort', 'ORG'), ('SceMiClockPort', 'ORG'), ('SceMiClockPort', 'ORG'), ('Ratio', 'PERSON'), ('RatioDenominator', 'ORG'), ('SceMiClockPort', 'ORG'), ('1/1', 'CARDINAL'), ('RatioDenominator', 'ORG'), ('4.1.4', 'CARDINAL'), ('51', 'CARDINAL'), ('Duty Cycle', 'PERSON'), ('SceMiClockPort', 'ORG'), ('Formal Functional Specification\nFunctional Requirements Specification: Standard Co-Emulation Modeling Interface', 'ORG'), ('SCE-MI', 'ORG'), ('61', 'CARDINAL'), ('1/1', 'CARDINAL'), ('4.1.4', 'CARDINAL'), ('51', 'CARDINAL'), ('Controlled Reset Cycles\n', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('ClockPort', 'ORG'), ('SCE', 'ORG'), ('API', 'ORG'), ('4.3.4', 'CARDINAL'), ('70', 'CARDINAL'), ('4.3', 'CARDINAL'), ('Software', 'ORG'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('SCE', 'ORG'), ('SCE', 'ORG'), ('SCE', 'ORG'), ('API', 'ORG'), ('62', 'CARDINAL'), ('94', 'CARDINAL'), ('C++', 'NORP'), ('SceMiclass', 'ORG'), ('4.3.1', 'CARDINAL'), ('Primitive Data Types', 'ORG'), ('API', 'ORG'), ('API', 'ORG'), ('4.3.2', 'CARDINAL'), ('Miscellaneous Interface', 'PERSON'), ('4.3.2.1', 'CARDINAL'), ('ec', 'ORG'), ('API', 'ORG'), ('SCE-MI', 'ORG'), ('SceMiErrorType', 'GPE'), ('SceMiOK', 'PERSON'), ('SceMiErrorType Type', 'ORG'), ('errorHandler', 'PERSON'), ('Formal Functional Specification\nFunctional Requirements Specification: Standard Co-Emulation Modeling Interface', 'ORG'), ('SCE-MI', 'ORG'), ('63', 'CARDINAL'), ('API', 'ORG'), ('NULL', 'ORG'), ('API', 'ORG'), ('API', 'ORG'), ('C++', 'NORP'), ('NULL', 'ORG'), ('second', 'ORDINAL'), ('API', 'ORG'), ('API', 'ORG'), ('SceMiErrorType', 'GPE'), ('only two', 'CARDINAL'), ('SceMiOK', 'PERSON'), ('API', 'ORG'), ('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('4.3.2.2', 'CARDINAL'), ('SceMiIC', 'PERSON'), ('Warning Handling', 'PERSON'), ('Info Handling', 'PERSON'), ('Formal Functional Specification\n64', 'ORG'), ('94', 'CARDINAL'), ('SCE', 'ORG'), ('info handling', 'PERSON'), ('SceMiInfoType', 'ORG'), ('SceMiIC', 'PERSON'), ('SceMiInfoType Type', 'ORG'), ('SceMiIC', 'PERSON'), ('info handler', 'PERSON'), ('API', 'ORG'), ('SceMiIC', 'PERSON'), ('SceMiIC', 'ORG'), ('API', 'ORG'), ('SceMiInfoType', 'ORG'), ('SceMiErrorHandler', 'ORG'), ('section 4.3.2.1', 'LAW'), ('62', 'CARDINAL'), ('SCE', 'ORG'), ('Formal Functional Specification\nFunctional Requirements Specification: Standard Co-Emulation Modeling Interface', 'ORG'), ('SCE-MI', 'ORG'), ('65', 'CARDINAL'), ('94\x7fAnything', 'CARDINAL'), ('API', 'ORG'), ('API', 'ORG'), ('SceMiMessageData', 'ORG'), ('API', 'ORG'), ('API', 'ORG'), ('4.3.3', 'CARDINAL'), ('SCE', 'ORG'), ('4.3.3.1', 'CARDINAL'), ('Version Discovery', 'PRODUCT'), ('SCE', 'ORG'), ('-1', 'ORG'), ('SCE', 'ORG'), ('4.3.3.2', 'CARDINAL'), ('ec', 'ORG'), ('SCE', 'ORG'), ('Formal Functional Specification', 'ORG'), ('66', 'CARDINAL'), ('94', 'CARDINAL'), ('SCE', 'ORG'), ('70', 'CARDINAL'), ('4.3.3.3', 'CARDINAL'), ('ec', 'ORG'), ('SCE', 'ORG'), ('ec', 'ORG'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('SceMiMessageInPortProxy', 'PERSON'), ('59', 'CARDINAL'), ('Formal Functional Specification\nFunctional Requirements Specification: Standard Co-Emulation Modeling Interface', 'ORG'), ('SCE-MI', 'ORG'), ('67', 'CARDINAL'), ('94Context', 'CARDINAL'), ('SceMiMessageInPortProxy', 'PERSON'), ('IsReady', 'PERSON'), ('IsReady', 'PERSON'), ('NULL', 'ORG'), ('SCE', 'ORG'), ('48', 'CARDINAL'), ('NULL', 'ORG'), ('4.3.3.5', 'CARDINAL'), ('SceMi::BindMessageOutPort', 'GPE'), ('ec', 'ORG'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('59', 'CARDINAL'), ('SceMiMessageOutPortBinding', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('SceMiMessageData', 'ORG'), ('Formal Functional Specification\n68', 'ORG'), ('94', 'CARDINAL'), ('SCE', 'ORG'), ('IsReady', 'PERSON'), ('77', 'CARDINAL'), ('NULL', 'ORG'), ('ec', 'ORG'), ('CPU', 'ORG'), ('SCE', 'ORG'), ('SCE', 'ORG'), ('ServiceLoop', 'ORG'), ('ServiceLoop', 'ORG'), ('NULL', 'ORG'), ('0', 'CARDINAL'), ('at least one', 'CARDINAL'), ('ServiceLoop', 'ORG'), ('4.3.3.6.1Example', 'CARDINAL'), ('ServiceLoop', 'ORG'), ('ServiceLoop', 'ORG'), ('ServiceLoop', 'ORG'), ('Formal Functional Specification\nFunctional Requirements Specification', 'ORG'), ('SCE-MI', 'ORG'), ('69', 'CARDINAL'), ('ServiceLoop', 'ORG'), ('0', 'CARDINAL'), ('ServiceLoop', 'ORG'), ('ServiceLoop', 'ORG'), ('0', 'CARDINAL'), ('ServiceLoop', 'ORG'), ('1', 'CARDINAL'), ('ServiceLoop', 'ORG'), ('ServiceLoop', 'ORG'), ('ServiceLoop', 'ORG'), ('1', 'CARDINAL'), ('1', 'CARDINAL'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('4.3.3.6.3Example', 'CARDINAL'), ('ServiceLoop', 'ORG'), ('At Least 1 Message\nAlternatively', 'CARDINAL'), ('ServiceLoop', 'ORG'), ('at least 1', 'CARDINAL'), ('Formal Functional Specification', 'ORG'), ('70', 'CARDINAL'), ('94', 'CARDINAL'), ('SCE-MI)To', 'ORG'), ('0', 'CARDINAL'), ('ServiceLoop', 'ORG'), ('0', 'CARDINAL'), ('g, &haveProcessedAtLeast1Message', 'ORG'), ('0', 'CARDINAL'), ('least//', 'ORG'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('1', 'CARDINAL'), ('1', 'CARDINAL'), ('1', 'CARDINAL'), ('ServiceLoop', 'ORG'), ('4.3.4', 'CARDINAL'), ('API', 'ORG'), ('59', 'CARDINAL'), ('4.3.3.2', 'CARDINAL'), ('65', 'CARDINAL'), ('4.3.4.1', 'CARDINAL'), ('SCE-API', 'ORG'), ('zero', 'CARDINAL'), ('API', 'ORG'), ('SCE', 'ORG'), ('Formal Functional Specification\nFunctional Requirements Specification: Standard Co-Emulation Modeling Interface', 'ORG'), ('SCE-MI', 'ORG'), ('71', 'CARDINAL'), ('94So', 'CARDINAL'), ('1', 'CARDINAL'), ('2', 'CARDINAL'), ('2', 'CARDINAL'), ('5', 'CARDINAL'), ('width', 'GPE'), ('SCE', 'ORG'), ('SCE', 'ORG'), ('section 4.2.1', 'LAW'), ('59', 'CARDINAL'), ('integer', 'PERSON'), ('4.3.4.2 Parameter Set Semantics', 'ORG'), ('TransactorName String Name', 'PERSON'), ('PortName String Name', 'PERSON'), ('PortWidth', 'ORG'), ('Integer Width', 'PERSON'), ('TransactorName String Name', 'PERSON'), ('PortName String Name', 'PERSON'), ('PortWidth', 'ORG'), ('Integer Width', 'PERSON'), ('PortPriority Integer Priority', 'ORG'), ('Integer Numerator', 'PERSON'), ('Integer Denominator', 'PERSON'), ('Integer High', 'PERSON'), ('Integer Low', 'PERSON'), ('Integer Phase', 'PERSON'), ('ClockBinding TransactorName String Name', 'ORG'), ('Formal Functional Specification\n72', 'ORG'), ('94', 'CARDINAL'), ('SCE', 'ORG'), ('ClockBinding', 'ORG'), ('TransactorName', 'ORG'), ('ClockBinding', 'ORG'), ('Clock', 'ORG'), ('HDL', 'ORG'), ('4.3.4.3', 'CARDINAL'), ('ec', 'ORG'), ('4.3.4.4', 'CARDINAL'), ('Formal Functional Specification\nFunctional Requirements Specification: Standard Co-Emulation Modeling Interface', 'ORG'), ('SCE-MI', 'ORG'), ('73', 'CARDINAL'), ('944.3.4.5  Accessors', 'CARDINAL'), ('ec', 'ORG'), ('ec', 'ORG'), ('ec', 'ORG'), ('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('ec', 'ORG'), ('ec', 'ORG'), ('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('section 4.3.4.1', 'DATE'), ('70', 'CARDINAL'), ('Formal Functional Specification\n74', 'ORG'), ('94', 'CARDINAL'), ('SCE', 'ORG'), ('Two', 'CARDINAL'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('SceMiMessageData', 'ORG'), ('SceMiMessageOutPort', 'ORG'), ('SceMiMessageOutPort', 'ORG'), ('72', 'CARDINAL'), ('4.3.5.1', 'CARDINAL'), ('SceMiMessageInPortProxy &messageInPortProxy', 'ORG'), ('ec', 'ORG'), ('4.3.5.2', 'CARDINAL'), ('1', 'CARDINAL'), ('0', 'CARDINAL'), ('33,32', 'CARDINAL'), ('71', 'CARDINAL'), ('0', 'CARDINAL'), ('1', 'CARDINAL'), ('Formal Functional Specification\nFunctional Requirements Specification: Standard Co-Emulation Modeling Interface', 'ORG'), ('SCE-MI', 'ORG'), ('75', 'CARDINAL'), ('944.3.5.3', 'CARDINAL'), ('ec', 'ORG'), ('ec', 'ORG'), ('0', 'CARDINAL'), ('0', 'CARDINAL'), ('1', 'CARDINAL'), ('ec', 'ORG'), ('LSB’s', 'ORG'), ('ec', 'ORG'), ('WidthInWords', 'ORG'), ('ec', 'ORG'), ('ec', 'ORG'), ('LSB', 'ORG'), ('SCE', 'ORG'), ('1/1', 'CARDINAL'), ('64', 'CARDINAL'), ('Formal Functional Specification', 'ORG'), ('76', 'CARDINAL'), ('94', 'CARDINAL'), ('SCE', 'ORG'), ('SceMiMessageInPortProxy', 'PERSON'), ('SceMiMessageInPortProxy', 'PERSON'), ('SceMiMessageData &data', 'ORG'), ('ec', 'ORG'), ('4.1.2', 'CARDINAL'), ('47', 'CARDINAL'), ('4.3.6.2', 'CARDINAL'), ('ec', 'ORG'), ('4.3.3.4', 'CARDINAL'), ('66', 'CARDINAL'), ('4.3.6.3', 'CARDINAL'), ('SceMiMessageInPortProxy::PortWidth', 'PERSON'), ('PortWidth', 'ORG'), ('Formal Functional Specification\nFunctional Requirements Specification: Standard Co-Emulation Modeling Interface', 'ORG'), ('SCE-MI', 'ORG'), ('77', 'CARDINAL'), ('944.3.6.4', 'CARDINAL'), ('4.3.7', 'CARDINAL'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('4.3.3.5', 'CARDINAL'), ('67', 'CARDINAL'), ('SceMiMessageData', 'ORG'), ('SceMiMessageData', 'ORG'), ('4.2.1.1', 'DATE'), ('61', 'CARDINAL'), ('SystemC', 'CARDINAL'), ('Notice', 'ORG'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('4.3.2.1', 'CARDINAL'), ('62', 'CARDINAL'), ('SCE', 'ORG'), ('ec', 'ORG'), ('4.3.3.5', 'CARDINAL'), ('67', 'CARDINAL'), ('Formal Functional Specification', 'ORG'), ('78', 'CARDINAL'), ('94', 'CARDINAL'), ('SCE-MI)4.3.7.3 Accessors', 'ORG'), ('SceMiMessageOutPort', 'ORG'), ('PortWidth', 'ORG'), ('SceMiMessageOutPort', 'ORG'), ('4.3.7.4', 'CARDINAL'), ('4.4', 'CARDINAL'), ('Software', 'ORG'), ('SCI-MI', 'ORG'), ('ANSI', 'ORG'), ('C++', 'CARDINAL'), ('API', 'ORG'), ('section 4.3', 'LAW'), ('61', 'CARDINAL'), ('the C API', 'PERSON'), ('the C++ API', 'FAC'), ('section 4.3', 'LAW'), ('61.Formal', 'CARDINAL'), ('Functional Specification\nFunctional Requirements Specification: Standard Co-Emulation Modeling Interface', 'ORG'), ('SCE-MI', 'ORG'), ('79', 'CARDINAL'), ('944.4.1', 'CARDINAL'), ('ServiceLoopHandler', 'PERSON'), ('SceMiOK', 'PERSON'), ('SceMiErrorType', 'GPE'), ('ec', 'ORG'), ('SceMiInfoType', 'ORG'), ('SceMiInfoType', 'ORG'), ('SceMiIC', 'ORG'), ('SceMiIC', 'PERSON'), ('SceMiMessageData', 'ORG'), ('C++ API', 'TIME'), ('ec', 'ORG'), ('80', 'CARDINAL'), ('94', 'CARDINAL'), ('SCE', 'ORG'), ('4.4.2.1', 'CARDINAL'), ('errorHandler', 'PERSON'), ('4.4.2.2', 'CARDINAL'), ('Warning Handling', 'PERSON'), ('Info Handling', 'PERSON'), ('4.4.3', 'CARDINAL'), ('Version Discovery', 'PRODUCT'), ('4.4.3.2', 'CARDINAL'), ('SceMiInit', 'ORG'), ('ec', 'ORG'), ('4.4.3.3', 'CARDINAL'), ('ec', 'ORG'), ('4.4.3.4', 'CARDINAL'), ('ec', 'ORG'), ('4.4.3.5', 'CARDINAL'), ('ec', 'ORG'), ('SCE-MI', 'ORG'), ('81', 'CARDINAL'), ('ec', 'ORG'), ('4.4.4', 'CARDINAL'), ('4.4.4.1', 'CARDINAL'), ('ec', 'ORG'), ('Formal Functional Specification\n82', 'ORG'), ('94', 'CARDINAL'), ('SCE', 'ORG'), ('4.4.4.3', 'CARDINAL'), ('ec', 'ORG'), ('ec', 'ORG'), ('ec', 'ORG'), ('ec', 'ORG'), ('ec', 'ORG'), ('4.4.5', 'CARDINAL'), ('SceMiMessageData - Message Data Object\n', 'ORG'), ('4.4.5.1', 'CARDINAL'), ('ec', 'ORG'), ('Formal Functional Specification\nFunctional Requirements Specification: Standard Co-Emulation Modeling Interface', 'ORG'), ('SCE-MI', 'ORG'), ('83', 'CARDINAL'), ('944.4.5.2 Destructor', 'ORG'), ('4.4.5.3', 'CARDINAL'), ('ec', 'ORG'), ('ec', 'ORG'), ('ec', 'ORG'), ('ec', 'ORG'), ('ec', 'ORG'), ('ec', 'ORG'), ('Formal Functional Specification', 'ORG'), ('84', 'CARDINAL'), ('94', 'CARDINAL'), ('SCE', 'ORG'), ('4.4.6.1', 'CARDINAL'), ('ec', 'ORG'), ('4.4.6.2', 'CARDINAL'), ('ec', 'ORG'), ('4.4.6.3', 'CARDINAL'), ('4.4.7', 'CARDINAL'), ('4.4.7.1 Replacing Port Binding', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('ec', 'ORG'), ('4.4.7.2', 'CARDINAL'), ('SceMiMessageOutPortProxyTransactorName', 'ORG'), ('Formal Functional Specification\nFunctional Requirements Specification: Standard Co-Emulation Modeling Interface', 'ORG'), ('SCE-MI', 'ORG'), ('85', 'CARDINAL'), ('BCA', 'ORG'), ('DUT', 'ORG'), ('2', 'CARDINAL'), ('9', 'CARDINAL'), ('BCA', 'ORG'), ('3', 'CARDINAL'), ('11', 'CARDINAL'), ('CoWare', 'PRODUCT'), ('SystemC', 'CARDINAL'), ('Ikos', 'PERSON'), ('DUT', 'ORG'), ('SceMiClockPort', 'ORG'), ('Verilog', 'PRODUCT'), ('Bridge.v', 'ORG'), ('Co-Emulation', 'ORG'), ('RTL', 'ORG'), ('86', 'CARDINAL'), ('94', 'CARDINAL'), ('SCE-MI)section', 'ORG'), ('1.4', 'CARDINAL'), ('3', 'CARDINAL'), ('1', 'CARDINAL'), ('6', 'CARDINAL'), ('DUT', 'ORG'), ('DUT', 'ORG'), ('DUT', 'ORG'), ('Controlled Time\nTime', 'ORG'), ('Co-Simulation\nExecution', 'ORG'), ('CoWare’s', 'PERSON'), ('section 1.4', 'LAW'), ('3', 'CARDINAL'), ('HDL', 'ORG'), ('API', 'ORG'), ('SCE', 'ORG'), ('RTCSCE-MIgate', 'ORG'), ('UTC', 'ORG'), ('RTC', 'ORG'), ('Functional Specification\nFunctional Requirements Specification: Standard Co-Emulation Modeling Interface', 'ORG'), ('SCE-MI', 'ORG'), ('87', 'CARDINAL'), ('94Cycle Stamping\n', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('0', 'CARDINAL'), ('See 4.1.4.1', 'ORG'), ('52', 'CARDINAL'), ('0', 'CARDINAL'), ('See 4.1.4.1', 'ORG'), ('52', 'CARDINAL'), ('DUT Proxy', 'PERSON'), ('DUT', 'ORG'), ('DUT', 'ORG'), ('3', 'CARDINAL'), ('11', 'CARDINAL'), ('DUT', 'ORG'), ('Hardware Model\nModel', 'PERSON'), ('CPU', 'ORG'), ('SCE-MIHardware', 'ORG'), ('CPU IP', 'ORG'), ('94', 'CARDINAL'), ('DUT', 'ORG'), ('SCE', 'ORG'), ('SCE', 'ORG'), ('SCE', 'ORG'), ('SceMiMessageOutPort', 'ORG'), ('SceMiClockPort', 'ORG'), ('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('DUT', 'ORG'), ('Verilog', 'PRODUCT'), ('SCE', 'ORG'), ('Software Model\nModel', 'PERSON'), ('SCE-MI', 'ORG'), ('89', 'CARDINAL'), ('C++', 'PERSON'), ('ISS', 'ORG'), ('CoWare', 'ORG'), ('SystemC', 'CARDINAL'), ('HDL', 'ORG'), ('SCE', 'ORG'), ('DUT', 'ORG'), ('DUT', 'ORG'), ('Clock', 'ORG'), ('SCE', 'ORG'), ('Uncontrolled Reset\n', 'PERSON'), ('SCE', 'ORG'), ('SCE', 'ORG'), ('Uncontrolled Time\nTime', 'ORG'), ('Formal Functional Specification\n90', 'ORG'), ('94', 'CARDINAL'), ('SCE', 'ORG'), ('18', 'CARDINAL'), ('ClockPort', 'ORG'), ('cclock4_1', 'LOC'), ('SceMiClockPort', 'ORG'), ('ClockNum=1', 'GPE'), ('1/1', 'CARDINAL'), ('#128', 'MONEY'), ('64', 'MONEY'), ('MessageOut', 'ORG'), ('SceMiMessageOutPort', 'ORG'), ('UclockUreset', 'ORG'), ('UclockUreset', 'ORG'), ('UclockUreset', 'ORG'), ('DutInData', 'ORG'), ('DutInCtrl DutInCtrl', 'PERSON'), ('DutInData', 'ORG'), ('DutInData', 'ORG'), ('DutInCtrl DutInCtrl', 'PERSON'), ('2', 'CARDINAL'), ('1', 'CARDINAL'), ('SceMiClockPort\nCclockCreset#(3', 'ORG'), ('4', 'DATE'), ('1', 'DATE'), ('75', 'DATE'), ('25', 'DATE'), ('30', 'DATE'), ('8)', 'CARDINAL'), ('SCE-MI', 'ORG'), ('91', 'CARDINAL'), ('0', 'CARDINAL'), ('8', 'CARDINAL'), ('SceMiClockPort', 'ORG'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('three', 'CARDINAL'), ('2/1', 'CARDINAL'), ('50%', 'PERCENT'), ('0', 'CARDINAL'), ('8', 'CARDINAL'), ('cclock4_1', 'ORG'), ('SceMiClockPort', 'ORG'), ('ClockNum=3', 'PRODUCT'), ('4/1', 'CARDINAL'), ('75%', 'PERCENT'), ('30%', 'PERCENT'), ('8', 'CARDINAL'), ('TxTransactor', 'PRODUCT'), ('Bridge.u1', 'PERSON'), ('ClockNum=1', 'CARDINAL'), ('TxTransactor', 'PRODUCT'), ('64', 'CARDINAL'), ('RxTransactor', 'PRODUCT'), ('cclock4_1', 'PERSON'), ('RxTransactor', 'ORG'), ('128.Formal', 'CARDINAL'), ('94', 'CARDINAL'), ('VHDL', 'PERSON'), ('Bridge', 'PERSON'), ('Structural of Bridge', 'ORG'), ('TxTransactor', 'FAC'), ('DutInCtrl', 'PERSON'), ('DutInData', 'ORG'), ('std_logic_vector(31', 'ORG'), ('std_logic_vector(31', 'ORG'), ('0', 'CARDINAL'), ('TxTransactor', 'FAC'), ('TxDUT', 'ORG'), ('DutInCtrl', 'PERSON'), ('DutInData', 'ORG'), ('std_logic_vector(31', 'ORG'), ('std_logic_vector(31', 'ORG'), ('Rst', 'PERSON'), ('TxDUT', 'ORG'), ('RxTransactor', 'PERSON'), ('DutInCtrl', 'PERSON'), ('DutInData', 'ORG'), ('std_logic_vector(31', 'ORG'), ('std_logic_vector(31', 'ORG'), ('0', 'CARDINAL'), ('RxTransactor', 'PERSON'), ('RxDUT', 'PERSON'), ('DutInCtrl', 'PERSON'), ('DutInData', 'ORG'), ('std_logic_vector(31', 'ORG'), ('std_logic_vector(31', 'ORG'), ('Clk', 'PERSON'), ('RxDUT', 'PRODUCT'), ('std_logic_vector(31', 'ORG'), ('rxDutInCtrl', 'GPE'), ('rxDutOutCtrl', 'GPE'), ('std_logic_vector(31', 'ORG'), ('TxTransactor', 'FAC'), ('SceMiClockPort', 'ORG'), ('2', 'CARDINAL'), ('2', 'CARDINAL'), ('1', 'DATE'), ('50', 'DATE'), ('50', 'DATE'), ('0', 'DATE'), ('8', 'CARDINAL'), ('cresetDivideBy4', 'GPE'), ('SceMiClockPort', 'ORG'), ('3', 'CARDINAL'), ('4', 'DATE'), ('1', 'DATE'), ('75', 'DATE'), ('25', 'DATE'), ('30', 'DATE'), ('8', 'CARDINAL'), ('SCE-MI', 'ORG'), ('93', 'CARDINAL'), ('94library', 'CARDINAL'), ('TxTransactor', 'FAC'), ('DutInCtrl', 'PERSON'), ('std_logic_vector(31', 'ORG'), ('std_logic_vector(31', 'ORG'), ('0', 'CARDINAL'), ('TxTransactor', 'FAC'), ('std_logic(63', 'GPE'), ('0', 'CARDINAL'), ('DutInCtrl', 'PERSON'), ('DutInData', 'ORG'), ('std_logic_vector(31', 'ORG'), ('std_logic_vector(31', 'ORG'), ('Uclk', 'PERSON'), ('TxTransactor', 'FAC'), ('DutInCtrl', 'PERSON'), ('DutInData', 'ORG'), ('DutOutCtrl', 'PERSON'), ('64', 'CARDINAL'), ('1', 'CARDINAL'), ('2', 'CARDINAL'), ('1', 'CARDINAL'), ('Functional Specification', 'ORG'), ('94', 'CARDINAL'), ('94', 'CARDINAL'), ('SCE', 'ORG'), ('VHDL SceMiMacros', 'ORG'), ('SCE-MI', 'ORG'), ('PortWidth', 'ORG'), ('SceMiMessageOutPort', 'ORG'), ('PortWidth', 'ORG'), ('PortPriority', 'ORG'), ('10', 'CARDINAL'), ('SceMiClockPort', 'ORG'), ('ClockNum', 'ORG'), ('1', 'CARDINAL'), ('1', 'CARDINAL'), ('1', 'CARDINAL'), ('0', 'CARDINAL'), ('100', 'CARDINAL'), ('0', 'CARDINAL'), ('ResetCycles      ', 'LAW'), ('8', 'CARDINAL'), ('ClockNum', 'ORG'), ('1', 'CARDINAL'), ('Ureset', 'ORG')], 'noun_phrases': ['94Functional Requirements Specification', '(SCE-MI', 'feedback contributions', 'the SCE-API Technical Group', 'Copyright', 'c', 'all rights', 'No part', 'this publication', 'a retrieval system', 'any form', 'any means', 'electronic, mechanical, photocopy', 'recording', 'the prior written permission', 'the \ncopyright holder', 'This document', 'NDA', 'the SCE-API consortium', 'Abstract', 'This document', 'a proposal', 'a standard C/C++ modeling interface', 'emulators', 'other verification platforms', 'The interface', 'multiple communication channels', 'software models', 'a host workstation', 'a \ndevice', 'test', 'DUT', 'a structural hardware netlist', 'a \nverification platform', 'an emulator', 'The channel end points', 'message ports', 'the DUT model', 'message port proxies', 'the software models', 'Inc.', 'San Jose', 'CA 95119SCE-API\nStandard Co-Emulation API \nConsortium\nRevision 1.9SCE-API Version 1.0Introduction', '94 Functional Requirements Specification', 'Standard Co-Emulation Modeling Interface', 'SCE-MI)1.0 Introduction', '1.1 Purpose', 'an urgent need', 'the EDA industry', 'the exploding verification requirements', 'SoC \ndesign teams', 'the industry', 'verification performance', 'the form', 'a variety', 'emulation', 'rapid prototyping platforms', 'the problem', 'them', 'SoC modeling environments', 'their full performance potential', 'Existing standard verification interfaces', 'the needs', 'design teams', 'A new type', 'interface', 'the verification challenges', 'the next 10 years', 'This document', 'a proposal', 'a multichannel communication interface', 'that', 'these challenges', 'This new interface', 'the needs', 'both emulation', 'users', 'emulation suppliers', '1.1.1 Emulation Customer Problems', 'SCE-API\n•All emulators', 'the market', 'proprietary APIs', 'The proliferation', 'APIs', 'it', 'software-based verification products', 'the different emulators', 'the solutions', 'customers', 'This', 'low productivity', 'low return', 'investment', 'ROI', 'emulator customers', 'who', 'their own solutions', '\x7fThe emulation “APIs', 'which', 'gate-level and not system-level verification', '\x7fThe industry', 'an API', 'which', 'full advantage', 'emulation performance', '1.1.2 Emulation Suppliers Problems', 'Solved\n\x7fCustomers', 'building applications', 'proprietary APIs', '\x7fTraditional simulator APIs', 'programmable language interface', 'PLI', 'VHDL PLI', 'emulators', '\x7fThird parties', 'building applications', 'proprietary APIs', '1.2 Scope\nThis document', 'members', 'the Standard Co-Emulation API', '(SCE-API) technical \ncommittee', 'The committee members', 'a consortium', 'EDA customers', 'EDA tool suppliers', 'the creation', 'a breakthrough high-performance common emulation API', 'The founding participants', 'the consortium', 'Aptix', 'CoWare', 'Ikos Systems', 'Mentor Graphics', 'ST Microelectronics', 'Synopsys', 'TransEDA', 'The scope', 'this document', 'what', 'the Standard \nCo-Emulation API', 'Modeling Interface', '(SCE-MI', 'This modeling interface', 'several parts', 'the whole SCE-API standard', 'the future', 'SCE-API', 'additional parts', 'such features', 'debug', 'control', 'code coverage', 'This document', 'an overall use model', 'the SCE-MI', 'a tutorial', 'this \nuse model', 'a formal functional specification', 'the SCE-MI API', 'itself', 'Future revisions', 'the document', 'the feedback', 'members', 'the SCE-API technical committee', 'It', 'the document', 'a relatively quick evolution phase', 'which', 'a common industry standard', 'that', 'simulation and emulation tool vendors', 'plug-and-play high speed verification solutions', 'users', 'SoC design teams', 'Introduction\nFunctional Requirements Specification', 'Standard Co-Emulation Modeling Interface', 'SCE-MI', '941.3 Revision History', '1.4 Definitions', 'Acronyms', 'Abbreviations\nA formal glossary', 'terms', 'this document', 'the appendices', 'Some', 'the acronyms', 'the document', 'BCA  - Bus Cycle Accurate model', 'RTL model\nBCASH  - CoWare style Bus Cycle Accurate SHell modelRevision # Date', 'Summary', 'revision', '1.0 12-11-00 Duaine Pryor Initial draft', 'discussions', 'SCE-API kickoff \nmeeting', 'that', 'Oct.', 'Paris', 'France', '1.2 1-15-01 John Stickley Revised document', 'feedback', 'action \nitems', 'second SCE-API meeting', 'Dec', 'Cupertino', 'CA', '1.3 2-2-01 John Stickley Revised document', 'feedback', 'e-\nmail review', 'SCE-API committee', 'the revi-\nsion 1.2 release', 'Routed tutorial sec-\ntion', '1.4 2-16-01 John Stickley', 'Susan RossIncorporated comments', 'committee', 'dur-\ning SCE-API phase 1 ratification process', 'Added \nminor corrections', 'converted hand drawn figures', 'electronic drawings', '1.5 5-6-01 John Stickley Corrections', 'SceMiParameters accessors', 'tion', 'controlled reset semantics', 'clarification', 'controlled clock semantics', 'call-\nback function pointer types', 'port proxies', 'VHDL macro data types', 'feedback', '1.5 changes', 'added bit \naccessors', 'data object', 'version', 'mat', 'major.minor.minor', 'major.major.minor', '1.7 10-19-01 John Stickley Added clarification', 'the \ng() function', 'ServiceLoop', 'added note', 'memory \nallocation', 'deletion', 'ReplaceBind-', 'ing', 'SceMiMessagePort[In/\nOut]Proxy classes', 'added info message callback \nhandler support', 'added clarification', 'parameters database structure', 'clarification', 'input \nready semantics', '1.8 11-14-01 John Stickley Incorporated feedback', 'corrections', 'above.1.9 2-26-02 John Stickley Added support', 'don’t care duty cycle', 'clarifica-\ntions', 'duty cycles', 'clock ratios', 'Changed default duty cycles', 'Added explanation', 'clock ratios', 'clock frequencies', 'Added section', 'multi-clock alignment', 'Minor modifications', 'the SceMiIC info message handler \nstructure', '94 Functional Requirements Specification', 'Standard Co-Emulation Modeling Interface', 'SCE-MI)BFM  - Bus Functional Model\nDUT  - Device', 'Design', 'Test\nHDL  - Hardware Description Language', 'Verilog', 'VHDL', 'ISS - Instruction Set Simulator\nRTC  - Register Transfer Level C model\nSCE-API  - Standard Co-Emulation API\nSCE-MI  - Standard Co-Emulation API - Modeling Interface\nUT', 'untimed C model\n1.5 References\n1.Functional Specification', 'SystemC', '2.0 - Synopsys', 'Inc.', 'CoWare, Inc.', 'Frontier Design, Inc.', 'CoWare N2C User Manual  - CoWare, Inc.', 'IEEE Standard Hardware Description Language', 'the Verilog Hardware Description \nLanguage', 'IEEE', 'Std', 'IEEE Computer Society', 'IEEE Standard VHDL Language Reference Manual', 'IEEE', 'IEEE Computer \nSociety', '1.6 Overview', 'a modeling interface', 'that', 'multiple channels', 'communication', 'that', 'software models', 'system behavior', 'structural models', 'implementation', 'a device', 'test', 'DUT', 'Each communication channel', 'untimed messages', 'arbitrary abstraction', 'its two end points', '“ports', 'a channel', 'These message channels', 'software models', 'software proxy models', 'port interfaces', 'the hardware side', 'the design', 'The means', 'software models', 'a software modeling and simulation environment', 'SystemC', 'which', 'the scope', 'this document', 'the software side', 'a system', 'several different levels', 'abstraction', 'untimed, cycle accurate, and even gate level', 'the focus', 'the SCE-MI', 'purely untimed software models', 'an RTL or gate level DUT', 'This', 'the following recommendations', 'the API', '\x7fDo', 'it', 'event', 'sub-cycle accurate simulation environments', '\x7fIt', 'to bridge cycle accurate simulation environments', '\x7fIt', 'an untimed simulation environment', 'a cycle accurate simulation environment', 'many references', 'the document', 'SystemC', 'the modeling environment', 'untimed \nsoftware models', 'This', 'SystemC', 'modeling', 'the cycle accurate RTL abstraction level', 'it', 'untimed modeling', 'it', 'use', 'the examples', 'this document', 'Introduction\nFunctional Requirements Specification', 'Standard Co-Emulation Modeling Interface', 'SCE-MI', '941.6.1 Performance Goals', 'the software  side', 'the described interface', 'its ability', 'any C/C++ \nmodeling environment', 'it', 'SystemC', 'reference', 'its hardware  side', 'undue throttling', 'an emulator', 'a co-modeling session run', 'this document', 'the term emulation', 'emulator', 'a structural or RTL model', 'a DUT', 'an emulator', 'rapid prototype', 'other simulation environment', 'software HDL simulators', 'That', 'the focus', 'the design', 'this interface', 'communication bottlenecks', 'that', 'software models', 'an emulator', 'them', 'a slower software HDL simulator', 'even an HDL accelerator', 'Such bottlenecks', 'the performance', 'an emulator', 'which', 'some implementations', 'the interface', 'others', 'nothing', 'the specification', 'the interface', 'itself', 'that', 'it', 'such bottlenecks', 'this reason', 'the communication channels', 'herein', 'the idea', 'a single message', 'a channel', 'a software \nmodel', 'dozens', 'hundreds', 'clocked events', 'the hardware side', 'the channel', 'it', 'thousands', 'clocked events', 'the hardware side', 'the content', 'a message', 'the hardware', 'that', 'an untimed software model', '1.6.2 Document Layout', 'The document', 'the following three major chapters', '\x7fChapter', 'An overall description', 'model', 'the SCE Modeling Interface', 'SCE-MI', '\x7fChapter', 'A tutorial', 'that', 'the use model', 'a simple application', '\x7fChapter', 'A formal functional specification', 'the API', 'itself', '1.6.3 Document Conventions', 'references', 'actual literal names', 'that', 'source code', 'identifiers', 'that', 'part', 'the API', 'file names', 'other literal names', 'courier  font', '\x7fKey concepts words', 'phrases', 'a good chance', 'any italicized  \ntext', 'a definition', 'the glossary', 'the reader', 'a more detailed meaning', 'a term', 'Overall Description', 'Use Model', '94 Functional Requirements Specification', 'Standard Co-Emulation Modeling Interface', 'SCE-MI)2.0 Overall Description', '2.1 High Level Description', 'Figure', 'a high level view', 'SCE-MI', 'untimed software \nmodels', 'structural hardware transactor', 'DUT models', 'FIGURE', 'High Level View', 'Run Time Components', 'The SCE-MI', 'a transport infrastructure', 'the emulator and host workstation sides', 'each channel', 'that', 'transactor  models', 'the emulator', 'C (untimed or RTL) models', 'the \nworkstation', 'it', 'purposes', 'this document', 'the term emulator', 'any simulator', 'RTL or gate-level models', 'software HDL simulators', 'These interconnects', 'the form', 'message channels', 'that', 'the software side', 'the hardware side', 'the SCE-MI infrastructure', 'Each message channel', 'two ends', 'The end', 'the software side', 'a message port proxy', 'which', 'a C++ object', 'that', 'API access', 'the channel', 'The end', 'the hardware side', 'a  message port macro', 'that', 'a transactor', 'other components', 'the transactor', 'Each message channel', 'either an input', 'an output channel', 'respect', 'the hardware side', 'It', 'message channels', 'unidirectional or bidirectional busses', 'the sense', 'hardware signals', 'network sockets', 'that', 'message passing protocols', 'It', 'the job', 'the transactors', 'abstraction gaskets', 'that', 'messages', 'input \nchannels', 'the software side', 'sequences', 'cycle accurate events', 'that', 'the DUT', 'the other direction', 'flow', 'recompose sequences', 'events', 'the DUT', 'messages', 'output channels', 'the software side', 'DUT\n C/C++', 'Model\nUTC Model\nRTC Model\nUTC Model\nSoftware Side', 'host workstation', 'Hardware Side', 'emulator)SCE-MI InfrastructureMessage Port \nProxy 1\nMessage Port \nProxy 2\nMessage Port \nProxy 3Transactor 2Transactor 1 Message \nPort 1\nMessage \nPort 2\nMessage \nPort 3\nClock/Reset\nGeneration', 'Control', 'SystemCOverall', 'Description', 'Use Model\nFunctional Requirements Specification', 'SCE-MI', '94In addition', 'the SCE-MI infrastructure', 'clock (and reset) generation', 'clock control', 'handshake signals', 'the transactor', 'This', 'the transactor', 'controlled time', 'message composition and decomposition operations', '2.1.1 Support', 'Multi-Threaded Environments', 'The SCE-MI', 'multi-threaded environments', 'SystemC', 'it', 'single-threaded environments', 'simple C programs', 'A special service \nloop function', 'section 4.3.3.6', 'page', 'the SCE-MI', 'that', 'an \napplication', 'the SCE-MI infrastructure', 'an opportunity', 'its communication channels', 'It', 'this function', 'that', 'input messages', 'the hardware side', 'output messages', 'the appropriate software models', 'no thread specific code', 'the service loop function', 'the SCE-MI', 'a \nmulti-threaded environment', 'this function', 'a dedicated thread', 'the interface', 'other threads', 'a single-threaded environment', 'the service loop function', 'the \napplication code', 'strategically placed points', 'it', 'CPU cycles', 'the SCE-MI infrastructure', 'it', 'its messages channels', '2.2 Users', 'the Interface\nA major goal', 'this specification', 'the needs', 'three target audiences', 'each', 'a distinct interest', 'their use', 'the interface', 'The target audiences', '\x7fEnd user\n\x7fTransactor implementor\n\x7fSCE-MI infrastructure implementor\n2.2.1 End User', 'The end user', 'a bridge', 'a software testbench', 'that', 'high level', 'untimed , algorithmic software models', 'a hardware DU', 'that', 'the RTL, cycle accurate level', 'abstraction', 'end users', 'the need', 'a “gasket', 'that', 'these two levels', 'abstraction', 'they', 'the creation', 'these abstraction bridges', 'the end users', 'the details', 'SCE-MI API', 'the hardware side', 'they', 'the  transactor implementor', 'next section', 'predefined transactor  models', 'that', 'their DUT', 'This', 'any requirement', 'them', 'any', 'the SCE-MI hardware-side interface macros', 'section', 'page', 'possibly the \nSceMiClockPort  macro', 'whose interface', 'all', 'it', 'a clock', 'a reset', 'the software side', 'the end users', 'the transactor implementors', 'them', 'plug-and-play  software models', 'custom', 'a software modeling environment', 'Such models', 'the details', 'the SCE-MI software side', 'interface', 'the rest', 'the software testbench', 'Overall Description', 'Use Model', '94 Functional Requirements Specification', '(SCE-MI)2.2.2 Transactor Implementor', 'the interface', 'the SCE-MI', 'its implementation', 'The job', 'the transactor implementor', 'plug-and-play transactor models', 'the hardware \nside', 'proxy models', 'the software side', 'that', 'end users', 'their \nuntimed software models', 'their RTL-represented DUT', 'the transactor implementor', 'proxy models', 'the software side', 'that', 'untimed “sockets', 'the transactors', 'the models', 'any other vendor', 'supplied, stand-alone IP models', 'the details', 'not only two different abstraction levels', 'possibly two different verification platforms', 'SystemC', 'an emulator', 'the implementations', 'the models', 'They', 'appropriate object code', 'netlists', 'RTL code', 'configuration files', 'all necessary documentation', '2.2.3 SCE-MI Infrastructure Implementor', 'The SCE-MI infrastructure implementor', 'a working implementation', 'an \nSCE-MI', 'that', 'some vendor supplied verification platform', 'Any distributed product release', 'the infrastructure implementor', 'both the software side', 'the hardware side components', 'the SCE-MI', 'such a release', 'complaint', 'it', 'all \nthe requirements', 'this specification', '2.3 Bridging Levels', 'Modeling Abstraction', 'The central goal', 'this specification', 'an interface', 'two modeling environments', 'each', 'which', 'a different level', 'modeling abstraction', 'we', 'a testbench', 'several, possibly independent models', 'that', 'a DUT', 'different interface points', 'Figure', 'such a system', 'Such a configuration', 'a processor DUT', 'that', 'some communications interfaces', 'that', 'an ethernet adapter', 'PCI interface', 'a USB interface', 'The testbench', 'several models', 'that', 'these interfaces', 'their protocols', 'packets', 'them', 'These packets', 'messages', 'the intent', 'the processor DUT’s ability', 'them', 'The system', 'Figure', 'the untimed  level', 'abstraction', 'the SystemC software modeling environment', 'Overall Description', 'Use Model\nFunctional Requirements Specification', 'Standard Co-Emulation Modeling Interface', 'SCE-MI', '94FIGURE', 'Untimed Software Testbench', 'DUT Models', 'we', 'cycle accurate RTL models', 'the DUT model', 'it', 'gates', 'that', 'a high speed emulation platform', 'we', 'this', 'we', 'them', 'the unaltered, untimed testbench models', 'a way', 'the untimed level', 'abstraction', 'the bus cycle', 'accurate  (BCA)  level', 'we', 'the purely untimed system', 'Figure', 'the direct coupling', 'the testbench models', 'the untimed DUT model', 'an abstraction bridge', 'order', 'the still untimed system testbench model', 'what', 'a emulator resident', ', RTL-represented DUT', 'Figure', 'this new configuration', 'This bridge', 'a set', 'DUT proxy  models', 'a set', 'message channels', 'which', 'transaction conduits', 'the software simulator', 'the emulator', 'message \ninput', 'output', 'ports', 'a set', 'user', 'transactors', 'The SCE-MI infrastructure', 'the task', 'a transport layer', 'that', 'delivery', 'messages', 'the message port proxy  and message port  ends', 'each channel', 'Messages', 'input channels', 'the transactors', 'message input ports', 'TB Model', 'Untimed\nTestbench', 'Model 1 TB Model N-1DUT ModelOverall Description', 'Use Model', '94 Functional Requirements Specification', 'Standard Co-Emulation Modeling Interface', 'output channels', 'the DUT proxy software models', 'message output port \nproxies', 'that', 'them', 'the rest', 'the testbench', 'they', 'original untimed \nDUT model', 'Figure', 'fact', 'the testbench models', 'the messages', 'a totally different abstraction level', 'The DUT input proxies', 'the job', 'untimed messages', 'various C models', 'them', 'the message input port proxies', 'transport', 'the hardware side', 'The DUT output proxies', 'callbacks', 'that', 'the message output port proxies', 'arrival', 'messages', 'the hardware side', 'other words', 'the SCE-MI infrastructure', 'these messages', 'the specific \nDUT proxy models', 'which', 'they', 'this discussion', 'the context', 'users', 'the interface', 'section', 'page', 'the end user', 'the DUT proxy models', 'the software side', 'Figure', 'the transactor models', 'the hardware side', 'the transactor implementor  authors', 'the proxy and transactor models', 'the SCE-MI message port', 'control components', 'them', 'those models', 'the end user', 'Overall Description', 'Use Model\nFunctional Requirements Specification', 'Standard Co-Emulation Modeling Interface', 'SCE-MI', '94FIGURE', 'Multichannel Abstraction Bridge Architecture\n2.3.3 Messages', 'Transactions', 'this point', 'it', 'sense', 'more detail', 'what', 'a message', 'it', 'an \nuntimed software modeling environment', 'the discussion', 'the implied meaning', 'a message', 'it', 'a unit', 'data', 'arbitrary size', 'abstraction', 'a channel', 'User Defined DUT \nProxy\nAbstraction BridgeUntimed\nTestbench ModelsSCE-MI Infrastructure User', 'Model', '(RTL', 'Port Proxy', 'TB Model', 'TB Model 1 TB Model N-1Message Output\nPort Proxy 0\nMessage Input\nPort Proxy 1\nMessage Output\nPort Proxy N-1', 'Xactor', 'Message Input', 'DUT', 'Use Model', '94 Functional Requirements Specification', 'Standard Co-Emulation Modeling Interface', 'SCE-MI)In', 'a purely untimed modeling environment', 'messages', 'specific clocks', 'events', 'they', 'arbitrary data types', 'abstraction', 'a simple bit', 'something', 'a C++ class', 'even some aggregate', 'objects', 'It', 'this form', 'messages', 'value', 'reference', 'abstract ports', 'fully untimed software models', 'the sort', 'Figure', 'substantially more detail', 'reference', 'messages', 'an SCE-MI message channel', 'their content', 'a large bit vector', 'the DUT proxy model', 'a message', 'a message output channel', 'a DUT output proxy model', 'it', 'an abstract C++ data type', 'this point', 'it', 'presentation', 'the abstract output ports', 'SystemC terminology', 'the DUT proxy', 'the connected software testbench models', 'the hardware side', 'a message', 'the message input channel', 'many \ndozens', 'hundreds', 'clocks', 'event activity', 'It', 'the job', 'the transactor', 'this decomposition', 'message data content', 'sequences', 'clocked events', 'that', 'the DUT hardware model inputs', 'output messages', 'it', 'the job', 'the transactor', 'possibly hundreds to thousands', 'clocked events', 'the DUT hardware model', 'them', 'serialized bit streams', 'that', 'the software side', 'de', '-', 'serialization', 'abstract data types', 'the most part', 'the term message', 'transaction', 'some contexts', 'transaction', 'infrastructure overhead content', 'addition', 'user payload data', 'a lower layer', 'the interface', 'whereas, the term message  denotes', 'only user payload data', 'the implications', 'the transactor’s job', 'message bit streams', 'clocked \nevents', 'it', 'the ability', 'controlled time', 'these operations', 'the controlled clock', 'that', 'the DUT', 'the operations', 'one', 'the transactor operations', 'terms', 'controlled clock cycles', 'they', 'edges', 'the controlled clock', 'This', 'the controlled time view', 'Figure', 'they', 'all cycles', 'the uncontrolled clock', 'the waveforms', 'the \nuncontrolled time  view', 'Figure', 'this view', 'the controlled clock', 'the DUT', 'controlled time', 'a system', 'multiple controlled clocks', 'possibly differing frequencies', 'multiple \ntransactors', 'them', 'these transactors', 'the option', 'any clock', 'this', 'all controlled clocks', 'the system', 'unison', 'all other transactors', 'that', 'themselves', 'the clock', 'the clocks', 'they', 'themselves', 'no need', 'the clock', 'this case', 'they', 'the number', 'uclocks', 'which', 'the cclocks', 'Figure 4.Overall Description', 'Use Model\nFunctional Requirements Specification', 'SCE-MI', '94FIGURE', 'the SCE-MI use model', 'the semantics', 'clock control', '\x7fAny transactor', 'the SCE-MI infrastructure', 'the controlled clock', 'controlled time', '\x7fAll transactors', 'the SCE-MI infrastructure', 'the controlled clock', '\x7fAny transactor', 'controlled time', 'operations', 'another transactor', 'the transactor', 'question', 'not itself', 'the clock', '\x7fA transactor', 'the controlled clock', 'operations', 'that', 'decomposition', 'composition', 'transactions', 'a message channel', '\x7fThe DUT', 'one or more controlled clocks', 'that', 'one or more transactors', '\x7fAll transactors', 'a free running uncontrolled clock', 'that', 'the SCE-MI hardware side', 'Time View\nuclock\ncclockuclock\nTransactor operation', 'controlled time', 'extra \nuncontrolled clock cycles', 'Transactor operation', 'edges', 'controlled clock', '94 Functional Requirements Specification', 'Standard Co-Emulation Modeling Interface', '(SCE-MI)2.4 Work Flow', 'four major aspects', 'work flow', 'a system verification', 'the SCE-\nMI environment', 'They', 'model compilation\n\x7fInfrastructure linkage\n\x7fHardware model elaboration', 'the workstation', 'a common C/C++ compiler', 'other sources', 'third party vendors', 'the form', 'IP', ', ISS simulators', 'The compiled models', 'the software side', 'the SCE-MI infrastructure', 'an executable program', '2.4.2 Infrastructure Linkage\nInfrastructure linkage', 'the process', 'that', 'a user description', 'the hardware', 'namely the source or \nbridge  netlist', 'that', 'the interconnect', 'the transactors', 'the DUT', 'the SCE-MI \ninterface components', 'that netlist', 'a form', 'emulation', 'Part', 'this compile process', 'additional structure', 'the bridge netlist', 'that', 'the user', 'netlist', 'the SCE-MI infrastructure implementation components', 'the infrastructure linker', 'the core', 'the SCE-MI interface macros', 'the hardware side', 'part', 'this process', 'the infrastructure linker', 'the parameters', 'the instantiated \ninterface macros', 'the user-supplied bridge netlist', 'them', 'the dimensions', 'the interface', 'the parameters', 'it', '\x7fNumber', 'transactors\n\x7fNumber', 'input and output channels', '\x7fWidth', 'each channel\n\x7fNumber', 'clocks', '\x7fClock ratios\n\x7fClock duty cycles', 'the final netlist', 'the infrastructure linker', 'it', 'the \nemulation platform', 'it', 'a form', 'the emulator', '2.4.3 Hardware Model Elaboration', 'The compiled netlist', 'the emulator', 'the \nsoftware', '2.4.4 Software Model Construction', 'Binding', 'The software', 'the software compilation phase', 'which', 'all the software models', 'the workstation process image space', 'construction', 'place', 'the software models', 'themselves', 'the message port proxies', 'special calls', 'the API', 'Parameters', 'these calls', 'a means', 'which', 'Overall Description', 'Use Model\nFunctional Requirements Specification', 'Standard Co-Emulation Modeling Interface', 'SCE-MI', '94port proxies', 'its associated message port macro', 'the hardware', 'the co-modeling session', '2.5 SCE-MI Interface Components', 'The SCE-MI run time environment', 'a set', 'interface components', 'both the  hardware side', 'the  software side', 'the interface', 'each', 'which', 'a distinct level', 'functionality', 'They', 'this section', 'each', 'more detail', 'this document', '2.5.1 Hardware Side Interface Components', 'The interface components', 'the SCE-MI hardware side  consist', 'a small set', 'macros', 'that', 'connection points', 'the transactors', 'the SCE-MI infrastructure', 'These', 'macros', 'all necessary aspects', 'the interface', 'the transactors', 'the DUT', 'the point', 'view', 'this specification', 'these macros', 'empty Verilog or \nVHDL models', 'clearly defined port and parameter interfaces', 'This', 'a software API specification', 'that', 'function prototypes', 'the API', 'their implementations', 'Future implementations', 'the interface', 'modeling hardware', 'RTL C', '(a.k.a. RTC', 'a C modeling language', 'SystemC', 'RTL Verilog', 'VHDL', 'Such implementations', 'the RTC equivalents', 'the same macros', 'this specification', 'Briefly', 'the four macros', 'the following interfaces', 'the transactors', 'DUT', '\x7fMessage input port interface\n\x7fMessage output port interface\n\x7fControlled clock and controlled reset generator interface', '\x7fUncontrolled clock', 'uncontrolled reset', 'Software Side Interface Components', 'The interface', 'SCE-MI infrastructure', 'the software side', 'a set', 'methods', 'which', 'the following functionality', '\x7fParameter access', '\x7fMessage input and output port proxy binding and callback registration\n\x7fRendezvous operations', 'the hardware side\n\x7fInfrastructure service loop polling function\n\x7fMessage input', 'function\n\x7fMessage output', 'addition', 'the C++ object oriented interface', 'a set', 'C API functions', 'the benefit', 'pure C applications', 'User’s Guide', 'Tutorial', '94 Functional Requirements Specification', 'Standard Co-Emulation Modeling Interface', '(SCE-MI)3.0 User’s Guide', 'Tutorial', '3.1 Hardware Side Interfacing', 'The hardware side interface', 'the SCE-MI', 'a set', 'parametrized macros', 'which', 'transactors', 'that', 'which', 'the SCE-MI infrastructure', 'The macros', 'the point', 'instantiation', 'crucial parameters', 'that', 'the dimensions', 'the SCE-MI bridge', 'software', 'the user', 'It', 'the job', 'the infrastructure \nlinker', 'the values', 'these parameters', 'implementation components', 'the macros', 'The following four macros', 'the hardware side interface', 'the SCE-MI', 'the transactors', 'the DUT', 'macro\n\x7fSceMiMessageOutPort  macro', 'macro\n\x7fSceMiClockPort  macro', 'Any number', 'these macros', 'the system', 'One SceMiMessageInPort  \nmacro', 'each required message input channel', 'one SceMiMessageOutPort  \nmacro', 'each output channel', 'Message port macro', 'bit-widths', 'the point', 'instantiation', 'Exactly one \nSceMiClockPort  macro', 'each defined clock', 'the system', 'This \nSceMiClockPort  macro instance', 'a set', 'parameters', 'a particular clock', 'The \nSceMiClockPort  macro', 'the top level', 'a controlled clock', 'the DUT', 'The SceMiClockPort  macro instance', 'a reference ClockNum  \nparameter', 'that', 'it', 'one or more counterpart SceMiClockControl  macros', 'one or more transactors', 'The SceMiClockControl  macro', 'its transactor', 'all clock \ncontrolling operations', 'its associated clock', 'These two macros', 'the \nClockNum  parameter', 'every SceMiClockPort  macro', 'a minimum', 'one \nSceMiClockControl  macro', 'it', 'The infrastructure linker', 'the user', 'these', 'the internally generated SCE-MI infrastructure', 'clock generation circuitry', 'The following parameters', 'the points', 'instantiation', 'the macros', 'the required \ndimensions', 'the SCE-MI infrastructure components', '4.2.1', 'page', 'more details', 'transactors\n\x7fNumber', 'input and output channels', 'each channel\n\x7fNumber', 'controlled clocks', '\x7fName', 'clock ratio', 'duty cycle', 'each controlled clock\nFigure', 'a simple example', 'a transactor', 'DUT', 'the hardware side \ninterface', 'the SCE-MI.User’s Guide and Tutorial\nFunctional Requirements Specification', 'Standard Co-Emulation Modeling Interface', 'SCE-MI', '94FIGURE', 'Connection', 'SCE-MI Macros', 'Hardware Side', 'Transactor', 'DUT', 'This example', 'a single transactor', 'a DUT', 'the software side', 'a SceMiMessageInPort', 'a SceMiMessageOutPort', 'addition', 'it', 'a single clock', 'that', 'the transactor', 'the SceMiClockControl  macro', 'This clock', 'the \nDUT', 'the top level', 'a SceMiClockPort  macro', 'A key point', 'this example', 'only the transactor implementor', 'page', 'all SCE-MI interface macros', 'the SceMiClockPort', 'the \ntransactor', 'the message port macros', 'the SceMiClockControl  macro', 'the end user', 'the transactor', 'itself', 'the SceMiClockPort  macro', 'The SceMiClockPort  macro instantiation', 'all the clock parameters', 'The numbers', 'Figure', 'the component instantiation label', '#', '8) cclock\nmap', 'the parameters', 'the SceMiClockPort  macro', 'page', 'They', '= 1\n\x7fRatioNumerator', '1TransmitReady', 'p1', '[ ]SceMiMessageOutPort#128 p2TxRdyIn\nUclock\nUreset', 'CclockNegEdgeEnabledRxRdyIn\nUclk\nRst', '[63:0]\nTxRdyOut\nRxRdyOut\nMessageOut', 'DutInCtrl\nDutInData', '[ ]\nClk\nRstd1\nDUT\nCclock\nCresetSceMiClockPort#(1', '8) cclockReadyForCclockNegEdge', '‘1’User’s Guide', 'Tutorial', '94 Functional Requirements Specification', 'Standard Co-Emulation Modeling Interface', 'SCE-MI)\x7fDutyHi', '= 50\n\x7fDutyLo', '= 50\n\x7fPhase', 'these parameters', 'the ClockNum  parameter', 'this particular clock', 'it', 'its 1 or more counterpart SceMiClockControl  macros', 'which', 'the same ClockNum  value', 'this case', 'addition', 'the clock specification parameters', 'the \ninfrastructure linker', 'the name', 'each clock', 'the instance label', 'each \nSceMiClockPort  instance', 'this case', 'message ports', 'a parametrized PortWidth  parameter', 'the  infrastructure linker', 'the following specific information', 'this \nnetlist', '\x7fSingle', 'transactor', '“Bridge.u1', 'top level module', '“Bridge', '“divide-by-1', 'controlled clock', '“cclock”\n\x7fControlled clock', 'a 1/1 ratio', 'which', 'implementation', 'the same frequency', 'the uncontrolled clock\n\x7fControlled clock', '50/50 duty cycle', '0 phase shift', 'a user', 'a don’t care duty cycle', 'page', 'details', '\x7fControlled reset', '8 controlled clock cycles', 'reset\n\x7fSingle SceMiMessageInPort', '“p1', 'bit-with', 'SceMiMessageOutPort', '“p2', 'bit-width', '128\nA more complicated example', 'that', 'two transactors', 'three clocks', 'Appendix B', 'page', 'The Routed  Tutorial\nThe Routed  tutorial documents', 'a real life example', 'that', 'the SCE-MI', 'untimed \nsoftware models', 'SystemC', 'hardware models', 'transactors', 'a DUT', 'RTL Verilog', 'This tutorial', 'the use model', 'the SCE-MI', 'a multi-threaded SystemC environment', 'It', 'some familiarity', 'the concepts', 'SystemC', 'abstract ports', 'autonomous threads', 'slave threads', 'module', 'port', 'definition', 'module instantiation', 'Reference', 'a description', 'these concepts', 'What', 'the Design', 'The \nRouted  design', 'a small design', 'that', 'air passengers', 'Origin', 'Destination', 'various interconnected Pipe s', 'Hubs', 'a RouteMap', 'this design', 'the \nOrigin s', 'Destination s', 'the transactors', 'the RouteMap  model', 'the DUT', 'Each Origin  \ntransactor interfaces', 'a SceMiMessageInPort', 'access', 'messages', 'the software \nside', 'Each Destination  transactor interfaces', 'a SceMiMessageOutPort', 'messages', 'the \nsoftware side', 'an OrigDest  module', 'that', 'both an Origin', 'Destination  transactor', 'it', 'User’s Guide and Tutorial\nFunctional Requirements Specification', 'Standard Co-Emulation Modeling Interface', 'SCE-MI', '94The “world', 'these Origin s', 'Anchorage', 'Cupertino', 'Noida', 'SealBeach', 'UK', 'Waltham', 'these Destination s', 'Anchorage', 'Cupertino', 'Maui', 'SealBeach', 'UK', 'Travel', 'any Origin', 'any Destination', 'the RouteMap', 'DUT', 'the following Pipe  interconnected Hubs', 'Chicago', 'Dallas', 'Newark', 'SanFran', 'Seattle', 'Each controlled clock cycle', 'one hour', 'travel or layover time', 'Figure', 'the Routed  world', 'User’s Guide and Tutorial\n20 of 94 Functional Requirements Specification', 'Standard Co-Emulation Modeling Interface', 'SCE-MI)FIGURE', 'The Routed  World\nThe numbers', 'the directed arcs', 'the travel time', 'hours', 'the indicated Pipe', 'Layover time', 'each Hub', 'two hours', 'The RouteMap', 'TeachRoute  messages', 'the entire system', 'the \nWaltham Origin  transactor', 'Each TeachRoute  message', 'a piece', 'information 3Legend\nHub\nPipe', 'travel time', 'Origin\nDestination\nOrigDestNoida14\nAnchorage', '5\nSeattle', '7UK\nAnchorage\nCupertino\nNoidaSealBeach\nUK', 'Standard Co-Emulation Modeling Interface', 'SCE-MI', 'a particular Hub', 'the route', 'its RouteTable  module', 'Figure', 'page', 'this simple mechanism', 'the software side RouteConfig  model', 'each Hub', 'its \nroutes', 'Waltham', 'it', 'turn', 'additional TeachRoute  tokens', 'Hubs', 'Waltham', 'other words', 'closer hubs', 'the RouteMap', 'routes', 'more distant hubs', 'This process', 'the entire mesh', 'which point', 'it', 'a backbone', 'all air travel activity', 'the route configuration', 'the testbench', 'the itineraries', '4 passengers', 'a \nperiod', '22 days', 'Each itinerary', 'several legs', 'each', 'scheduled departure', 'a specified \nOrigin', 'each', 'a specified Destination', 'The scheduled leg', 'a message', 'its designated Origin  transactor', 'It', 'the job', 'the transactor', 'the number', 'clocks', 'the \nspecified departure time', 'the token', 'the RouteMap  mesh', '3.2.2 System Hierarchy', 'The hierarchy', 'the whole system', 'the following subsections', '3.2.2.1 Software Side Hierarchy\nSystem', 'TestbenchCalendar', '> ClockAdvancer\nScheduler', 'OrigDest', 'Origin', 'Destination    \nRouteConfigSceMiDispatcher', 'the Calendar', 'Scheduler  software side models', 'the \nOrigDest', 'Origin', 'Destination  hardware side models', 'These interactions', 'SCE-MI \nmessage channels', 'Guide', 'Tutorial', '94 Functional Requirements Specification', 'Standard Co-Emulation Modeling Interface', 'SCE-MI)3.2.2.2 Hardware Side Hierarchy', 'Following', 'the hierarchy', 'the hardware side components', 'the Bridge  netlist', 'SceMiClockControl', 'Destination maui', 'dallasHub', 'newarkHub', 'sanFranHub', 'Funnel\nNozzle\nRouteTable\nPipe\nClockAdvancer', 'SceMiMessageInPortSceMiMessageOutPort\nSceMiClockControl\nNotice', 'the Bridge  level', 'only the SceMiClockPort  macro, transactor  components', 'the DUT', 'the Origin', 'Destination  transactors', 'the SceMiMessageInPort', 'SceMiMessageOutPort', 'SceMiClockControl  macros', 'The ClockAdvancer  transactor', 'both \nmessage input', 'output ports', 'addition', 'the required SceMiClockControl  macro', '3.2.3.1 Bridge', 'the hardware and software side', 'the design', 'Figure', 'this \ndiagram', 'the structure', 'the generalized abstraction bridge', 'Figure', 'page', 'The design', '13 message channels', 'all', 'Two (message input', 'output', 'the Calendar \n<-> ClockAdvancer connection', 'six message input channels', 'the  Scheduler <-> Origin \nconnections', 'five output channels', 'the Scheduler <-> Destination  connections', 'User’s Guide and Tutorial\nFunctional Requirements Specification', 'Standard Co-Emulation Modeling Interface', 'SCE-MI', '94FIGURE', 'The Bridge', 'The two software models', 'that', 'the hardware side', 'the Calendar  model', 'the \nScheduler  model', 'These models', 'message port proxies', 'which', 'them', 'direct access', 'the \nmessage channels', 'the Origin', 'Destination  transactors', 'the hardware side', 'These two \nsoftware models', 'the only ones', 'that', 'the SCE-MI link', 'They', 'the other models', 'SystemC abstract ports', 'the hardware side', 'a set', 'Origin', 'that', 'the message \nchannels', 'that', 'the Scheduler', 'route tokens', 'the DUT', 'Some locations', 'Anchorage', 'the UK', 'Origin', 'Destination', 'OrigDest', 'Out', 'Port\nProxyCalendar', 'AdvanceCalendar', 'Out\nPortClock', 'Models\nAnchorage\nMessage', 'Out', 'Port\nProxy\nNoida', 'Port', 'Out', 'Arrival', 'Message', '/OutPort\nMessage', 'Out', 'UK', '94 Functional Requirements Specification', 'Standard Co-Emulation Modeling Interface', 'a ClockAdvancer  transactor', 'that', 'the Calendar  model', 'The \nClockAdvancer', 'a stand-alone transactor', 'that', 'the DUT', 'Its only job', 'time', 'a time', 'section', '3.2.3.5', 'page', 'more details', '3.2.3.2 DUT and Transactor Interconnect\nFigure', 'a representative portion', 'the RouteMap', 'it', 'DUT components', 'the RouteMap  mesh', 'FIGURE', 'DUT and Transactor Interconnect\nOrigin\nTokenOut\nDestination\nTokenIn\nDestination\nTokenInP', 'ePipe 5\nP', 'ePipe 5\nP', 'ePipe 4Funnel', 'Standard Co-Emulation Modeling Interface', 'SCE-MI', '94Pipe s', 'two Hubs', 'an Origin', 'Destination  transactor', 'a Hub', 'primitive one hour', 'the proper length', 'one hour', 'travel', 'one clock', 'this diagram', 'a Pipe4  model', 'the Seattle Hub', 'Maui Destination', 'a four hour flight leg', 'travel', 'either direction', 'Anchorage', 'Seattle', 'a Pipe5', 'them', 'each direction', '3.2.3.3 DUT and Transactor Components\nFigure', 'the structure', 'the DUT and transactor components', 'FIGURE', 'DUT and Transactor Components\nMessageIn Port\nClockControl\nMessageOut Port\nClockControl\nMessageIn Port\nMessageOut PortOrigin', 'TokenInDestination', '32Transactor', 'Components DUT Components\nFunnel\nTokenIn0', 'TokenOut2TokenOut3Nozzle', 'TokenOut\nTokenIn\nRouteTableHub\n32\n32\n32\n323232\n32\n32\n32\nPipe\nTokenIn TokenOut32', '32\n‘TeachRoute', 'Token', '0307 1113\nDestination ID', 'Hub\nLearn Route ID\nAssociated Port ID‘Passenger Arrival', 'Origin', '4 IDPassenger ID', 'Departure15', 'Tutorial', '94 Functional Requirements Specification', 'Standard Co-Emulation Modeling Interface', 'SCE-MI)Each Origin  transactor', 'a clock control macro', 'a message input port macro', 'departure tokens', 'the Scheduler', 'the software side', 'Each', 'the \nTokenOut  port', 'the scheduled departure time', 'the Origin  transactor', 'a \nclock control macro', 'it', 'the clock', 'Its only use', 'the clock control macro', 'the \nReadyForCclock  signal', 'which', 'the cclock', 'it', 'cclocks', 'the scheduled departure time', 'a pending departure', 'Each Destination  transactor', 'a clock control macro', 'a message output port macro', 'arrival tokens', 'the Scheduler', 'the software side', 'The arrival tokens', 'a passenger', 'the RouteMap  mesh', 'a Destination', 'its TokenIn  port', 'section', 'page', 'a detailed description', 'the Destination  transactor', 'This transactor', 'detail', 'it', 'a simple example', 'clock control and message port interfacing', 'a 32-bit vector signal', 'no handshakes', 'the system', 'the tokens', '0s', 'the mesh', 'any given cycle', 'a \nHub', 'Destination', 'a non-0 value', 'its input port', 'it', 'it', 'that', 'Token formats', 'Figure', 'A departure', 'the passenger ID', 'destination ID', 'scheduled time', 'departure', 'the departure', 'the mesh', 'it', 'layover information', 'the IDs', 'all the \nHubs', 'its Destination', 'an arrival', 'The arrival', 'a complete record', 'layover information', 'that', 'the software side', 'the console', 'A \nHub', 'a Funnel', 'that', 'tokens', 'up to four different sources', 'a Nozzle', 'that', 'a token up to four different destinations', 'The Nozzle', 'a small RouteTable', 'that', 'the beginning', 'the simulation', 'information', 'TeachRoute  tokens', 'The Destination  Transactor', 'the DUT', 'the Clock\nThe Destination  transactor', 'tokens', 'a point', 'exit', 'the RouteMap', 'them', 'the message output port', 'The Destination  transactor', 'clock control', 'potentially successive tokens', 'the RouteMap', 'the TokenIn  input', 'this destination portal', 'It', 'the \nreadyForCclock', 'the event', 'a token', 'the message output port', 'it', 'tokens', 'it', 'the entire \nRouteMap', 'all tokens', 'the requesting Destination  transactors', 'The Verilog source code', 'the Destination  transactor', 'the following listing', 'Standard Co-Emulation Modeling Interface', 'SCE-MI', '94module', 'Destination', '( TokenIn', 'input', 'TokenIn;//', '[31:0] message', 'transmitReady', 'readyForCclock', 'destID = TokenIn[7:4', 'SceMiMessageOutPort', '#32 messageOutPort', 'Output', '---------------------------        .TransmitReady(transmitReady),      .ReceiveReady(receiveReady),\n        .Message(message) );\n    SceMiClockControl clockControl', 'Output', '( posedge uclock', 'if( ureset', '=', '=', 'readyForCclock', 'transmitReady', ';        end', 'DUT clock', 'It', 'this destination transactor', 'its pending token', 'the\n            //     DUT', 'it', 'tokens', 'subsequent DUT clocks', '( readyForCclock', '=', '=', 'acceptance', 'the token', 'we', 'the DUT clock', '( receiveReady', 'readyForCclock', 'message', 'TokenIn', 'transmitReady', 'if( token arrives', 'the assembly line', '(a.k.a. disable', 'the DUT', '=', '=', '}User’s Guide', 'Tutorial', '94 Functional Requirements Specification', 'Standard Co-Emulation Modeling Interface', 'SCE-MI)3.2.3.5', 'The ClockAdvancer  Transactor', 'Controlling Time Advance\nThe ClockAdvancer  transactor', 'controlled clocks', 'the requested number', 'cycles', 'a reply transaction', 'User’s Guide and Tutorial\nFunctional Requirements Specification', 'Standard Co-Emulation Modeling Interface', 'SCE-MI', '94The Verilog source code', 'the ClockAdvancer', 'module ClockAdvancer', 'wire', 'messageIn', 'messageOut', 'receiveReadyIn', 'messageIn[31:0', 'messageOut', '=', 'SceMiMessageInPort', 'Output', ');    SceMiMessageOutPort', '#32 messageOutPort', 'Output', ';\n    SceMiClockControl clockControl', 'Output', '.Ureset(ureset', 'readyForCclock', ';\n        end', 'a clock advance command - Initialize cycle counter', 'if( transmitReadyIn', 'transmitReadyOut', 'advanceDelta', 'Decrement cycle count', 'count', 'a response', 'the time', '( readyForCclock', '=', '=', '( receiveReadyOut', '=', 'the SceMiClockControl  macro references', 'that', 'the Destination  \ntransactor', 'the default ClockNum=1', 'This', 'the ClockAdvancer', 'the Destination  User’s Guide', 'Tutorial', '94 Functional Requirements Specification', 'Standard Co-Emulation Modeling Interface', 'SCE-MI)transactor share', 'the control', 'the same cclock', 'fact', 'only one cclock', 'the entire system', 'that', 'the default 1/1 ratio', 'Notice', 'the message output port', 'the data', 'that', 'it', 'This', 'the only thing', 'that', 'the software side', 'the ClockAdvancer', 'the cycle stamp', 'which', 'each message output response', 'page', '3.2.4', 'The Software Side', 'The software side', 'the Routed design', 'SystemC', 'C++', 'It', 'an \nexecutable program', 'that', 'the SCE-MI software side', 'The\n System  Model', 'Interconnect', 'SystemC Modules\nThe System  model', 'the top level “software netlist', 'SystemC modules', 'SC_MODULE', 'It', 'the construction', 'interconnect', 'the component models', 'A block diagram', 'the System model', 'Figure', 'FIGURE', 'Interconnect', 'SystemC Models\nTest Bench\nNewDay\nAnnounceArrivalAdvanceCalendar\nScheduleLeg\nLoadRouteMap\nDoneCalendar\nAdvanceCalendar\nAdvanceClockNewDay\nTodaysDate\nSceMi Dispatcher\nDoneScheduler\nTodaysDate\nScheduleLegLoadRouteAnnounceArrival\nRouteConfig\nLoadRouteMap LoadRoute\nAdvanceClock\nSceMi::ServiceLoop()Message Channel sTestbench ArchitectureUser’s Guide and Tutorial\nFunctional Requirements Specification', 'Standard Co-Emulation Modeling Interface', 'SCE-MI', '94Following', 'the source code', 'the System model', 'SC_MODULE', 'System', '<const Routed::ArrivalRecord', 'announceArrival', 'unsigned>                      advanceCalendar', 'sc_link_mp', 'const', 'sc_link_mp<>                              loadRouteMap', 'sc_link_mp', 'sc_link_mp', 'advanceClock', 'sc_link_mp', 'sc_link_mp<const Routed::Route *>         loadRoute', 'Module declarations', '*testbench', 'Calendar       *', '*scheduler', 'RouteConfig', '*routeConfig', 'SceMiDispatcher', 'SC_CTOR', '( System', 'new Testbench', 'testbench->NewDay', 'announceArrival', '( advanceCalendar', 'testbench->ScheduleLeg', 'loadRouteMap', 'testbench->Done', '( “calendar', 'calendar->AdvanceCalendar', 'advanceCalendar', 'calendar->AdvanceClock', 'advanceClock', 'todaysDate', 'new Scheduler', '(      todaysDate', 'scheduler->LoadRoute', 'announceArrival', 'routeConfig', '( “routeConfig', 'loadRouteMap', 'routeConfig->LoadRoute', 'loadRoute', 'advanceClock', 'SystemC interconnect channels', 'sc_link_mp<>  data types', 'These', 'abstract signals', 'that', 'abstract ports', 'The parametrized data type', 'each \nsc_link_mp', 'the data type', 'the message', 'the channel', 'an \noutput abstract port', 'an input abstract port', 'the todaysDate  channel', 'value” data type', 'some', 'the other channels', 'the announceArrival', 'reference” data types', 'Routed::ArrivalRecord', 'less User’s Guide', 'Tutorial', '94 Functional Requirements Specification', 'Standard Co-Emulation Modeling Interface', 'SCE', 'the message', 'value', 'no danger', 'the \nreceiver', 'the sender’s data', 'the sender’s data', 'scope', 'the receiver', 'a possibly dangling reference', 'messages', 'reference', 'care', 'their use', 'them', 'const  pointers', 'some',